Date,Tweet-text,Retweets,Likes,entities,topic,confidence,sentiment,sentiment_confidence
2019/04/10_17:08,From a big NBA fan congrats to future Hall of Famers Dwyane Wade and Dirk Nowitzki—not just all-time greats but class acts too.,20954,175133,"['NBA' 'ORG'],['Dwyane Wade' 'PERSON'],['Dirk Nowitzki' 'PERSON']",USA,0.5717242956161499,positive,0.8824763298034668
2019/04/04_12:23,Here’s a story about people doing good that's worth sharing: @BradPaisley and his wife @Kimwilliamspais saw food insecurity in Nashville and decided to do something about it. They just broke ground on a free grocery store to help families in need:https://apnews.com/2f5bdd226a674fd7bd9dca97c172475c …,15396,78627,"['@BradPaisley' 'PERSON'],['@Kimwilliamspais' 'PERSON'],['Nashville' 'GPE']",family,0.6450821757316589,positive,0.8164641261100769
2019/04/03_12:07,Great to see Chicago’s historic mayoral race between two highly qualified candidates. Congrats to our next mayor Lori Lightfoot—and Toni Preckwinkle campaigned hard and did us proud. I know that with our city’s heart and Lori’s leadership Chicago’s best days are still ahead.,8991,98094,"['Chicago' 'GPE'],['Lori Lightfoot' 'PERSON'],['Toni Preckwinkle' 'PERSON'],['Lori' 'PERSON'],['Chicago' 'GPE']",politics,0.6069708466529846,positive,0.9763973951339722
2019/04/02_06:08,Valerie is one of my oldest friends and advisors – she was by my side when I first decided to run for office and for every major moment of the presidency. @ValerieJarrett's voice has often inspired me and I know “Finding My Voice” will inspire others to lift their voices too.pic.twitter.com/nWTBDByMoz,6839,66187,"['Valerie' 'PERSON'],['@ValerieJarrett' 'PERSON'],['Finding My Voice' 'WORK_OF_ART']",family,0.807860791683197,positive,0.8658573627471924
2019/03/26_11:33,Last night I had the chance to meet with first-term Democrats in Congress—it's a young diverse class stocked with a bunch of my campaign and administration alums who’ve taken the torch. This group is going to be driving progress for a long time to come.pic.twitter.com/W5dDlDtNzE,14325,117989,"['Democrats' 'NORP'],['Congress' 'ORG']",politics,0.5769850611686707,positive,0.7819011211395264
2019/03/21_08:43,Just in the nick of time: My brackets have never been my one shining moment but here we go again. You can check out my #MarchMadness picks here: https://go.obama.org/2019-bracket pic.twitter.com/EcCUdnZjun,8457,59574,['#MarchMadness' 'EVENT'],USA,0.4360155165195465,neutral,0.5896584391593933
2019/03/20_07:20,And here are some ways to help cyclone victims in Mozambique Malawi and Zimbabwe:https://www.pbs.org/newshour/world/how-to-help-cyclone-victims-in-mozambique-malawi-and-zimbabwe …,8402,37269,"['Mozambique' 'GPE'],['Malawi' 'GPE'],['Zimbabwe' 'GPE'],['mozambique' 'GPE'],['zimbabwe' 'GPE']",climate change,0.7063242793083191,neutral,0.7800565361976624
2019/03/20_07:19,The floods in the Midwest and in southern Africa are heartbreaking. Suffering and loss on two sides of the world calls for solidarity and strength from all of us. Ask what you can do to help our fellow Americans and families in need. Here are some ideas:https://www.pbs.org/newshour/nation/how-to-help-those-affected-by-the-midwest-flooding …,18792,86957,"['Midwest' 'LOC'],['Africa' 'LOC'],['Americans' 'NORP'],['midwest' 'LOC']",USA,0.42692553997039795,neutral,0.5784199833869934
2019/03/17_06:56,In 2011 I visited the tiny town of Moneygall and got to walk around in the house where my great-great-great grandfather Falmouth Kearney lived his early life. I'll always be grateful for the warmth and generosity of the Irish people. Happy St. Patrick's Day! -Barack O’Bamapic.twitter.com/abDtarFbR5,23726,244904,"['Moneygall' 'GPE'],['Falmouth Kearney' 'PERSON'],['Irish' 'NORP'],['-Barack O’Bamapic.twitter.com/abDtarFbR5' 'PERSON']",family,0.7337457537651062,positive,0.9704992175102234
2019/03/15_06:15,Michelle and I send our condolences to the people of New Zealand. We grieve with you and the Muslim community. All of us must stand against hatred in all its forms.,111063,669878,"['Michelle' 'PERSON'],['New Zealand' 'GPE'],['Muslim' 'NORP']",family,0.7765297889709473,neutral,0.5624510645866394
2019/03/14_13:36,. @MichelleObama and I are rooting hard for Team USA as the Special Olympics World Games get underway this week. Our Special Olympians are terrific examples of America’s heart and drive.,13764,150080,"['@MichelleObama' 'PERSON'],['Team USA' 'ORG'],['the Special Olympics World Games' 'EVENT'],['America' 'GPE']",USA,0.948502242565155,positive,0.8890145421028137
2019/03/12_11:48,What a great moment. Happy 110th Virginia.https://twitter.com/MichelleObama/status/1105480037271289856 …,21986,253052,,family,0.5147920250892639,positive,0.9833715558052063
2019/03/10_18:02,Michelle and I send our deepest sympathies to all who knew the victims of today’s plane crash in Ethiopia.,35181,371801,"['Michelle' 'PERSON'],['Ethiopia' 'GPE']",family,0.5560070276260376,neutral,0.6416890025138855
2019/03/08_08:03,The Crew Dragon’s been on quite a ride since I last saw it—congrats to @NASA and @SpaceX on a successful return! We invested in the @Commercial_Crew program to strengthen the U.S. space program for the long haul and it’s great to see that happening.pic.twitter.com/Dsu5mZcaCZ,10923,130875,"['The Crew Dragon' 'PRODUCT'],['@NASA' 'ORG'],['@SpaceX' 'ORG'],['U.S.' 'GPE']",USA,0.564125120639801,positive,0.9745571613311768
2019/02/21_11:01,It’s up to all of us as citizens to make sure that the rules of democracy are fair—everywhere—because the next decade of our nation's progress is on the line. Join me and @allontheline in the fight against gerrymandering: http://allontheline.org .pic.twitter.com/rKchS3ltLI,21437,99024,['@allontheline' 'ORG'],politics,0.5364865660667419,neutral,0.5828182101249695
2019/02/20_20:41,Zion Williamson seems like an outstanding young man as well as an outstanding basketball player. Wishing him a speedy recovery.,32770,313064,['Zion Williamson' 'PERSON'],health,0.818465530872345,positive,0.9499024748802185
2019/02/14_10:32,Happy Valentine’s Day to the extraordinarily smart beautiful funny one and only @MichelleObama. It’s true; she does get down to Motown.pic.twitter.com/uypbZsEiqB,38486,421878,['@MichelleObama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.46148747205734253,positive,0.9769470691680908
2019/02/13_19:10,Don’t be sad it’s over be proud it taught us so much. Congrats to all the men and women of @NASA on a @MarsRovers mission that beat all expectations inspired a new generation of Americans and demands we keep investing in science that pushes the boundaries of human knowledge.,35599,298673,"['@NASA' 'ORG'],['@MarsRovers' 'PRODUCT'],['Americans' 'NORP']",USA,0.780487060546875,positive,0.957038402557373
2019/02/12_17:18,Happy 85th birthday to @RealBillRussell - the greatest champion in American sports and a lifelong warrior for justice.,12377,129038,"['@RealBillRussell' 'PERSON'],['American' 'NORP']",USA,0.6050808429718018,positive,0.9627336263656616
2019/02/07_20:03,We lost two great Americans today – Frank Robinson and John Dingell – citizens who inspired me and so many others by leading on the civil rights issues of our time opening doors to others and leaving it all on the field.,29136,241969,"['Americans' 'NORP'],['Frank Robinson' 'PERSON'],['John Dingell' 'PERSON']",USA,0.6998876929283142,neutral,0.5363540649414062
2019/02/01_08:08,As we celebrate Black History Month and Jackie Robinson’s 100th birthday we celebrate the life of all whose courage opened the gates for everybody and in the process made America better.pic.twitter.com/Fl9aDxqcGi,40360,250601,"['Jackie Robinson’s' 'PERSON'],['America' 'GPE']",USA,0.5313900709152222,positive,0.9205790162086487
2019/01/21_08:14,"I’ve always drawn inspiration from what Dr. King called life’s most persistent and urgent question: ""What are you doing for others?"" Let’s honor his legacy by standing up for what is right in our communities and taking steps to make a positive impact on the world.",162936,770070,['King' 'PERSON'],USA,0.4630735516548157,positive,0.8880981802940369
2018/12/29_08:15,Leaders like Moussa Kondo and Sandor Lederer who are each doing their part to fight corruption in their native countries of Mali and Hungary. Two people separated by continents but united in their pursuit of a more just transparent society.https://www.obama.org/fellowship/moussa-kondo-sandor-lederer/ …,3841,27248,"['Moussa Kondo' 'PERSON'],['Sandor Lederer' 'PERSON'],['Mali' 'GPE'],['Hungary' 'GPE']",politics,0.5613315105438232,neutral,0.5967079997062683
2018/12/29_08:15,Leaders like Dejah Powell who started an organization to bring health and wellness resources to communities on the South Side of Chicago expanding food access and providing people the space and time to take care of themselves.pic.twitter.com/tPW7NxTGLO,5169,35342,"['Dejah Powell' 'PERSON'],['the South Side' 'LOC']",health,0.9734089970588684,positive,0.5138150453567505
2018/12/25_06:14,Enjoy the holiday season with the ones you love. Michelle and I wish you a very Merry Christmas!pic.twitter.com/LKLqlYfFUw,93008,932946,['Michelle' 'PERSON'],family,0.9078690409660339,positive,0.9813543558120728
2018/12/19_13:48,Merry Christmas and happy holidays to the extraordinary kids families and staff at Children’s National. And thanks for humoring me as your stand-in Santa.https://twitter.com/childrenshealth/status/1075507032537620480 …,66367,401532,['Children’s National' 'ORG'],family,0.8649957776069641,positive,0.9805282950401306
2018/12/14_16:58,Joe is right. Head to http://healthcare.gov  before tomorrow’s deadline. And nice bracelet by the way.https://twitter.com/JoeBiden/status/1073716529336860673 …,33374,155294,['Joe' 'PERSON'],health,0.6247575283050537,positive,0.78508460521698
2018/12/10_07:40,No jump shots. No ferns. No memes. Not this time. I’m going to give it to you straight: If you need health insurance for 2019 the deadline to get covered is December 15. Go to http://HealthCare.gov  today and pass this on — you just might save a life.pic.twitter.com/8mHMsXGY0g,137703,349950,,business,0.6007939577102661,neutral,0.5298559069633484
2018/12/02_14:09,Happy Hanukkah! Over these eight nights we draw inspiration from light that can overpower any darkness and recommit ourselves to building a brighter future for our families our communities and our world. Chag Sameach from the Obama family to yours.,52168,413129,"['Hanukkah' 'EVENT'],['Chag Sameach' 'PERSON'],['Obama' 'PERSON']",family,0.6629056334495544,positive,0.9422736167907715
2018/11/30_21:36,America has lost a patriot and humble servant in George Herbert Walker Bush. While our hearts are heavy today they are also filled with gratitude. Our thoughts are with the entire Bush family tonight – and all who were inspired by George and Barbara’s example.pic.twitter.com/g9OUPu2pjY,68331,373228,"['America' 'GPE'],['George Herbert Walker Bush' 'PERSON'],['Bush' 'PERSON'],['George' 'PERSON'],['Barbara' 'PERSON']",USA,0.7752286195755005,positive,0.5340408682823181
2018/11/21_10:57,I am grateful for the next generation of leaders -- the young people who are tolerant creative idealistic and doing the work to create the world as it should be. Who understand that hope requires action. From the Obama family to yours Happy Thanksgiving.https://twitter.com/ObamaFoundation/status/1065309361906561025 …,40830,243529,['Obama' 'PERSON'],family,0.9256411790847778,positive,0.9764726758003235
2018/11/13_10:37,Of course @MichelleObama’s my wife so I’m a little biased here. But she also happens to be brilliant funny wise – one of a kind. This book tells her quintessentially American story. I love it because it faithfully reflects the woman I have loved for so long.pic.twitter.com/X0i9jja4TE,66013,539905,"['@MichelleObama' 'PERSON'],['American' 'NORP']",family,0.6319175958633423,positive,0.9726320505142212
2018/11/11_19:20,Michelle and I are heartbroken for everybody who’s lost so much in California and grateful for the heroism of the firefighters who’ve been risking their lives around the clock to save others. Please do what you can to help our fellow Americans in need:https://nyti.ms/2DdQB3c,55379,294025,"['Michelle' 'PERSON'],['California' 'GPE'],['Americans' 'NORP']",family,0.6740245223045349,neutral,0.47118446230888367
2018/11/11_08:14,To all our veterans and your families: thank you. There's no tribute that can truly match the magnitude of your service and sacrifice. But all of us can do our best to live up to the American values of service responsibility generosity and citizenship that you helped defend.,114086,675333,['American' 'NORP'],family,0.6684530377388,positive,0.8805767297744751
2018/11/07_08:13,Congratulations to everybody who showed up and participated in our democracy in record numbers yesterday. The change we need won’t come from one election alone – but it is a start. Last night voters across the country started it.pic.twitter.com/gNk4WkeJUn,52239,327018,,politics,0.5372822880744934,positive,0.9531537294387817
2018/11/06_08:26,Today is the day. Today it’s your turn to raise your voice to change the course of this country for the better. So make it count. Get out there and vote. Go to http://IWillVote.com  or call 833-336-VOTE to confirm where you can vote and check voting hours.pic.twitter.com/6xdMbKhwkr,39469,175002,,politics,0.5195016264915466,positive,0.6741169095039368
2018/11/05_10:46,When you vote you have the power to protect voting rights. To make sure our criminal justice system treats everyone equally under the law. To strengthen laws that protect women in the workplace from harassment – and make sure they’re paid equally.,14073,61358,,politics,0.8977808952331543,neutral,0.6742005348205566
2018/11/05_10:46,When we've been at such crossroads before Americans have made the right choice. Not because we sat back and waited for history to happen -- but because we marched and mobilized and voted. We made history happen.,11864,52906,['Americans' 'NORP'],USA,0.47129252552986145,neutral,0.5211233496665955
2018/11/05_10:46,Tomorrow’s elections might be the most important of our lifetimes. The health care of millions is on the ballot. Making sure working families get a fair shake is on the ballot. The character of our country is on the ballot.,141921,518200,,health,0.6912357211112976,positive,0.8357639312744141
2018/11/01_14:20,Speaking of preexisting conditions open enrollment starts today. If you or someone you know needs health care visit http://HealthCare.gov . Thanks to financial help most people can find plans for $75/month or less so check out your options and find a plan that works for you.pic.twitter.com/R52X9sgkbP,21909,56969,['http://HealthCare.gov' 'ORG'],health,0.6304292678833008,positive,0.5845605731010437
2018/11/01_11:32,While we're talking about preexisting conditions the ACA is the law that finally protected your coverage for preexisting conditions. Those protections and your health care are absolutely at stake on Tuesday. Vote for Democrats who’ll protect them.https://www.thecut.com/2018/10/republicans-dont-protect-preexisting-conditions.html …,22537,74309,"['ACA' 'LAW'],['Democrats' 'NORP']",health,0.7852663993835449,neutral,0.5605764985084534
2018/10/31_11:20,Not sure who and what you can vote for? Head over to http://votesaveamerica.com/ballot  to look up your state learn who's running to represent you which measures you can help decide and more. Read up and get ready to vote on November 6.,36823,98797,,politics,0.6146106719970703,neutral,0.8127053380012512
2018/10/30_08:44,Your vote can decide the health care of millions. Your voice can determine the character of our country. You have power — use it! In most states you don't even have to wait until Election Day to cast a ballot. Find out where you can vote before Nov. 6: http://IWillVote.com pic.twitter.com/hWkFHqi49K,25391,84380,,health,0.7403091192245483,neutral,0.5384334921836853
2018/10/27_14:54,We grieve for the Americans murdered in Pittsburgh. All of us have to fight the rise of anti-Semitism and hateful rhetoric against those who look love or pray differently. And we have to stop making it so easy for those who want to harm the innocent to get their hands on a gun.,187580,848414,"['Americans' 'NORP'],['Pittsburgh' 'GPE']",USA,0.6713387370109558,negative,0.806166410446167
2018/10/17_10:21,The last presidential election turned on fewer than 100000 votes in three states. More people go to Coachella. There’s no good excuse not to vote. Head over to http://Vote.org  to check your registration get your absentee ballot and find out where to vote on November 6.https://twitter.com/attn/status/1052577837968846848 …,100143,247603,['Coachella' 'GPE'],politics,0.6550900340080261,neutral,0.5852564573287964
2018/10/11_18:51,America is always at our best when we look out for each other. Please do what you can to help people recover and rebuild from Hurricane Michael.https://www.charitynavigator.org/index.cfm?bay=content.view&cpid=6806 …,18581,97697,"['America' 'GPE'],['Hurricane Michael.https://www.charitynavigator.org/index.cfm?bay=content.view&cpid=6806'
 'EVENT']",USA,0.8552213311195374,positive,0.6493752002716064
2018/10/03_12:08,Happy Anniversary @MichelleObama. For 26 years you’ve been an extraordinary partner someone who can always make me laugh and my favorite person to see the world with.pic.twitter.com/s8xoZ9j2YR,68489,693716,['@MichelleObama' 'PERSON'],family,0.6320300102233887,positive,0.9870243072509766
2018/10/01_09:46,Today I’m proud to endorse even more Democratic candidates who aren’t just running against something but for something—to expand opportunity for all of us and to restore dignity honor and compassion to public service. They deserve your vote:pic.twitter.com/NO5jnhX3XD,47143,213976,['Democratic' 'NORP'],politics,0.7519968748092651,positive,0.9505618810653687
2018/09/25_13:49,The antidote to government by a powerful few is government by the organized energized many. This National Voter Registration Day make sure you're registered vote early if you can or show up on November 6. This moment is too important to sit out.,100639,379371,,politics,0.5510309338569641,positive,0.5609023571014404
2018/09/11_06:52,We will always remember everyone we lost on 9/11 thank the first responders who keep us safe and honor all who defend our country and the ideals that bind us together. There's nothing our resilience and resolve can’t overcome and no act of terror can ever change who we are.,138625,761556,['9/11' 'EVENT'],USA,0.5474541187286377,positive,0.6102576851844788
2018/09/07_08:08,Today I’m at the University of Illinois to deliver a simple message to young people all over the country: You need to vote because our democracy depends on it. I hope you'll tune in at 11am CT: http://go.illinois.edu/live,47429,264989,['the University of Illinois' 'ORG'],politics,0.8249806761741638,neutral,0.4959774911403656
2018/08/29_12:54,Yesterday I met with high school students on Chicago’s Southwest side who spent the summer learning to code some pretty cool apps. Michelle and I are proud to support programs that invest in local youth and we’re proud of these young people.pic.twitter.com/dQnDgswCj5,56714,391476,"['Chicago' 'GPE'],['Michelle' 'PERSON']",family,0.5547091960906982,positive,0.9783124923706055
2018/08/26_14:40,Congratulations to Hawaii for winning the Little League World Series! You make America very proud. https://twitter.com/LittleLeague/status/1033829386116640773 …,33411,373102,"['Hawaii' 'GPE'],['the Little League World Series' 'EVENT'],['America' 'GPE']",USA,0.6301118731498718,positive,0.9744632244110107
2018/08/16_09:31,Aretha helped define the American experience. In her voice we could feel our history all of it and in every shade—our power and our pain our darkness and our light our quest for redemption and our hard-won respect. May the Queen of Soul rest in eternal peace.pic.twitter.com/bfASqKlLc5,130920,585900,"['Aretha' 'PERSON'],['American' 'NORP'],['the Queen of Soul' 'PERSON']",USA,0.6655674576759338,positive,0.599288821220398
2018/08/01_09:20,Today I’m proud to endorse such a wide and impressive array of Democratic candidates – leaders as diverse patriotic and big-hearted as the America they’re running to represent:pic.twitter.com/gWzalQhFas,53341,234581,"['Democratic' 'NORP'],['America' 'GPE']",USA,0.6852461099624634,positive,0.9706797003746033
2018/06/08_09:01,“Low plastic stool cheap but delicious noodles cold Hanoi beer.” This is how I’ll remember Tony. He taught us about food — but more importantly about its ability to bring us together. To make us a little less afraid of the unknown. We’ll miss him.pic.twitter.com/orEXIaEMZM,233350,1098227,"['Hanoi' 'GPE'],['Tony' 'PERSON']",family,0.8026647567749023,positive,0.7166902422904968
2018/05/28_09:02,We can never truly repay the debt we owe our fallen heroes. But we can remember them honor their sacrifice and affirm in our own lives those enduring ideals of justice equality and opportunity for which generations of Americans have given that last full measure of devotion.pic.twitter.com/pRxwmaMClL,112803,588155,['Americans' 'NORP'],USA,0.4824737012386322,neutral,0.5653609037399292
2018/05/13_07:32,Happy Mother’s Day to every mom out there especially the remarkable moms in my life @MichelleObama and my mother-in-law Marian Robinson.pic.twitter.com/n65fyWg7O8,57003,583492,"['@MichelleObama' 'PERSON'],['Marian Robinson.pic.twitter.com/n65fyWg7O8' 'PERSON']",family,0.8747443556785583,positive,0.9636586308479309
2018/05/08_12:40,There are few issues more important to the security of the US than the potential spread of nuclear weapons or the potential for even more destructive war in the Middle East. Today’s decision to put the JCPOA at risk is a serious mistake. My full statement: https://www.facebook.com/barackobama/posts/10155854913976749 …,129117,440854,"['US' 'GPE'],['the Middle East' 'LOC'],['JCPOA' 'GPE']",USA,0.6574124097824097,negative,0.7904534339904785
2018/04/23_12:13,These talented young people will create a better future not just in Africa but around the world. I can’t wait to spend some time with @ObamaFoundation Leaders and look forward to honoring the Mandela legacy in Johannesburg this summer.https://twitter.com/obamafoundation/status/988475935463759878 …,29949,198789,"['Africa' 'LOC'],['@ObamaFoundation' 'ORG'],['Mandela' 'PERSON'],['Johannesburg' 'GPE']",family,0.528995156288147,positive,0.9687305688858032
2018/04/17_17:44,Our statement on the passing of Former First Lady Barbara Bush:pic.twitter.com/MhTVYCL9Nj,49260,320292,['Barbara Bush' 'PERSON'],family,0.6442999839782715,neutral,0.8355924487113953
2018/03/25_08:34,Incredible to have a Chicago team in the Final Four. I’ll take that over an intact bracket any day! Congratulations to everybody @LoyolaChicago - let’s keep it going!,19676,223060,"['Chicago' 'GPE'],['the Final Four' 'EVENT'],['@LoyolaChicago' 'ORG']",family,0.6116805076599121,positive,0.9677519202232361
2018/03/24_10:07,Michelle and I are so inspired by all the young people who made today’s marches happen. Keep at it. You’re leading us forward. Nothing can stand in the way of millions of voices calling for change.,314091,1554820,['Michelle' 'PERSON'],family,0.7108179926872253,positive,0.9318022131919861
2018/03/19_14:48,Our most important task as a nation is to make sure all our young people can achieve their dreams. We’ve started this work with @MBK_Alliance but there’s so much more all of us have to do—government private sector academia & community leaders—to change the odds for our kids.https://twitter.com/upshotnyt/status/975774912764882946 …,26490,136499,,USA,0.49092695116996765,positive,0.7636837959289551
2018/03/12_11:12,Four years ago @MichelleObama and I had the privilege to host Lt. Cmdr. Dan Cnossen and his fellow Paralympians and Olympians at the White House. Today we’re so proud of him for winning gold and silver - while still representing the red white and blue.pic.twitter.com/evDCV7zehM,19142,171934,"['@MichelleObama' 'PERSON'],['Dan Cnossen' 'PERSON'],['Paralympians' 'NORP'],['Olympians' 'NORP'],['the White House' 'FAC']",USA,0.5030913352966309,positive,0.9406622648239136
2018/02/21_08:33,Billy Graham was a humble servant who prayed for so many - and who with wisdom and grace gave hope and guidance to generations of Americans.,33584,251675,"['Billy Graham' 'PERSON'],['Americans' 'NORP']",USA,0.4680093228816986,positive,0.688360333442688
2018/02/15_09:12,We are grieving with Parkland. But we are not powerless. Caring for our kids is our first job. And until we can honestly say that we're doing enough to keep them safe from harm including long overdue common-sense gun safety laws that most Americans want then we have to change.,363910,1287417,"['Parkland' 'EVENT'],['Americans' 'NORP']",family,0.48915162682533264,neutral,0.5690407156944275
2018/02/14_08:25,Happy Valentine’s Day @MichelleObama. You make every day and every place better.pic.twitter.com/aWvyytR7Mm,232868,1487065,,family,0.7537704706192017,positive,0.9880205988883972
2017/12/29_08:11,All across America people chose to get involved get engaged and stand up. Each of us can make a difference and all of us ought to try. So go keep changing the world in 2018.,111280,491998,['America' 'GPE'],USA,0.8316422700881958,positive,0.8391730785369873
2017/12/29_08:09,As we count down to the new year we get to reflect and prepare for what’s ahead. For all the bad news that seemed to dominate our collective consciousness there are countless stories from this year that remind us what's best about America.,170097,764562,['America' 'GPE'],USA,0.8459593057632446,positive,0.6962711811065674
2017/12/25_08:05,On behalf of the Obama family Merry Christmas! We wish you joy and peace this holiday season.pic.twitter.com/CNFUZrhrBj,241677,1435418,['Obama' 'PERSON'],family,0.9592801332473755,positive,0.9718084931373596
2017/12/12_16:17,Happy Hanukkah everybody from the Obama family to yours. Chag Sameach!,81053,669809,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['Chag Sameach!' 'PERSON']",family,0.9629130959510803,positive,0.9377608299255371
2017/12/11_12:16,Just got off a call to thank folks who are working hard to help more Americans across the country sign up for health coverage. But it's up to all of us to help spread the word: Sign up through this Friday at http://HealthCare.gov .https://twitter.com/getuscovered/status/940289973869215749 …,84205,220326,['Americans' 'NORP'],health,0.6968477368354797,positive,0.7987317442893982
2017/11/27_13:13,Michelle and I are delighted to congratulate Prince Harry and Meghan Markle on their engagement. We wish you a lifetime of joy and happiness together.,109989,1127258,"['Michelle' 'PERSON'],['Harry' 'PERSON'],['Meghan Markle' 'PERSON']",family,0.8041080236434937,positive,0.9861620664596558
2017/11/23_06:44,From the Obama family to yours we wish you a Happy Thanksgiving full of joy and gratitude.pic.twitter.com/xAvSQwjQkz,205459,1346777,['Obama' 'PERSON'],family,0.9517741203308105,positive,0.9829508662223816
2017/11/20_11:02,ME: Joe about halfway through the speech I’m gonna wish you a happy birth-- BIDEN: IT’S MY BIRTHDAY! ME: Joe. Happy birthday to @JoeBiden my brother and the best vice president anybody could have.pic.twitter.com/sKbXjNiEjH,482109,1955860,"['Joe' 'PERSON'],['Joe' 'PERSON']",family,0.8539628386497498,positive,0.9794233441352844
2017/11/08_05:25,This is what happens when the people vote. Congrats @RalphNortham and @PhilMurphyNJ . And congratulations to all the victors in state legislative county and mayors' races. Every office in a democracy counts!,70290,418336,"['@RalphNortham' 'PERSON'],['@PhilMurphyNJ' 'PERSON']",politics,0.8255175948143005,positive,0.9034377336502075
2017/11/06_17:02,Every election matters - those who show up determine our future. Go vote tomorrow!http://www.vote.org ,55919,188070,,politics,0.6166885495185852,positive,0.6376529932022095
2017/11/05_16:51,We grieve with all the families in Sutherland Springs harmed by this act of hatred and we’ll stand with the survivors as they recover...,92582,531414,['Sutherland Springs' 'GPE'],family,0.915157675743103,negative,0.524036705493927
2017/11/01_06:06,Starting today you can sign up for 2018 health coverage. Head on over to http://HealthCare.gov  and find a plan that meets your needs.https://twitter.com/getuscovered/status/925709097076449280 …,131255,249492,,health,0.7009636759757996,neutral,0.7107676863670349
2017/10/31_17:56,Michelle and I are thinking of the victims of today's attack in NYC and everyone who keeps us safe. New Yorkers are as tough as they come.,98963,684200,"['Michelle' 'PERSON'],['NYC' 'GPE'],['New Yorkers' 'NORP']",family,0.5980689525604248,neutral,0.5117791295051575
2017/10/23_15:03,I’ll let you and @ladygaga handle the singing and we’ll handle the donations. There’s still time to give: http://oneamericaappeal.org .https://twitter.com/georgehwbush/status/922485638846443520 …,52179,301107,,USA,0.45232218503952026,neutral,0.539520800113678
2017/10/16_15:59,I'm grateful to @SenJohnMcCain for his lifetime of service to our country. Congratulations John on receiving this year's Liberty Medal.,88233,657343,"['@SenJohnMcCain' 'PERSON'],['John' 'PERSON'],['Liberty Medal' 'WORK_OF_ART']",USA,0.5572543144226074,positive,0.9715479016304016
2017/10/02_05:41,Michelle & I are praying for the victims in Las Vegas. Our thoughts are with their families & everyone enduring another senseless tragedy.,378412,1647558,"['Michelle' 'PERSON'],['Las Vegas' 'GPE']",family,0.8670830726623535,neutral,0.48840057849884033
2017/09/29_19:22,Proud to cheer on Team USA at the Invictus Games today with my friend Joe. You represent the best of our country.pic.twitter.com/WBzcltmgqj,58258,494448,"['Team USA' 'ORG'],['the Invictus Games' 'EVENT'],['Joe' 'PERSON']",USA,0.8668404221534729,positive,0.9768218398094177
2017/09/25_16:36,Prosecutor soldier family man citizen. Beau made us want to be better. What a legacy to leave. What a testament to @JoeBiden.https://twitter.com/joebiden/status/912459460316188673 …,55891,320367,['Beau' 'PERSON'],family,0.7738330960273743,positive,0.6594134569168091
2017/09/19_19:30,Thinking about our neighbors in Mexico and all our Mexican-American friends tonight. Cuidense mucho y un fuerte abrazo para todos.,422157,1442382,"['Mexico' 'GPE'],['Mexican-American' 'NORP']",family,0.854274332523346,neutral,0.8165449500083923
2017/09/13_07:08,Michelle and I want the @ObamaFoundation to inspire and empower people to change the world. Here's how we're getting started this fall.https://twitter.com/obamafoundation/status/907938000113467392 …,62504,256067,"['Michelle' 'PERSON'],['@ObamaFoundation' 'ORG']",family,0.49830126762390137,positive,0.5966437458992004
2017/09/11_08:32,We remember everyone we lost on 9/11 and honor all who defend our country and our ideals. No act of terror will ever change who we are.,328609,1324399,['9/11' 'EVENT'],USA,0.657932460308075,neutral,0.49674540758132935
2017/09/08_14:34,Proud of these McKinley Tech students—inspiring young minds that make me hopeful about our future.pic.twitter.com/nqYC1mjjTB,30126,230971,['McKinley Tech' 'ORG'],USA,0.5013532042503357,positive,0.9815069437026978
2017/09/07_16:06,Americans always answer the call. http://OneAmericaAppeal.org pic.twitter.com/ktEvL6s89d,96699,325177,['Americans' 'NORP'],USA,0.8752495646476746,positive,0.6544960141181946
2017/09/05_11:52,To target hopeful young strivers who grew up here is wrong because they’ve done nothing wrong. My statement: http://www.facebook.com/barackobama/ ,367099,892817,,family,0.7255034446716309,negative,0.5656160116195679
2017/08/27_16:14,Thank you to all the first responders and people helping each other out. That's what we do as Americans. Here's one way you can help now.https://twitter.com/redcross/status/901546157238833152 …,235195,804044,['Americans' 'NORP'],USA,0.8290852308273315,positive,0.9458978176116943
2017/08/17_12:15,Michelle and I are thinking of the victims and their families in Barcelona. Americans will always stand with our Spanish friends. Un abrazo.,304873,1564593,"['Michelle' 'PERSON'],['Barcelona' 'GPE'],['Americans' 'NORP'],['Spanish' 'NORP']",family,0.5973830819129944,neutral,0.6798182129859924
2017/08/12_17:06,...For love comes more naturally to the human heart than its opposite. - Nelson Mandela,393547,1369281,['Nelson Mandela' 'PERSON'],family,0.5153418779373169,positive,0.5560877323150635
2017/06/22_12:41,Health care has always been about something bigger than politics: it's about the character of our country. https://www.facebook.com/barackobama/posts/10154996557026749 …,126220,432442,,health,0.9223266243934631,neutral,0.6609611511230469
2017/06/18_08:09,Of all that I've done in my life I'm most proud to be Sasha and Malia's dad. To all those lucky enough to be a dad Happy Father's Day!https://twitter.com/michelleobama/status/876454925131288580 …,244181,1320947,"['Sasha' 'PERSON'],['Malia' 'PERSON']",family,0.8212317228317261,positive,0.9734780192375183
2017/06/02_10:35,On this National Gun Violence Awareness Day let your voice be heard and show your commitment to reducing gun violence.pic.twitter.com/eXkV4WmkqA,69620,380004,,USA,0.4482741057872772,neutral,0.6779797077178955
2017/05/29_06:09,Forever grateful for the service and sacrifice of all who fought to protect our freedoms and defend this country we love.pic.twitter.com/y7IQltbEz9,127303,685817,,USA,0.6962700486183167,positive,0.9638637900352478
2017/05/27_06:15,Good to see my friend Prince Harry in London to discuss the work of our foundations & offer condolences to victims of the Manchester attack.https://twitter.com/kensingtonroyal/status/868418451970379776 …,72412,482482,"['Prince Harry' 'PERSON'],['London' 'GPE'],['Manchester' 'GPE']",family,0.6004635095596313,positive,0.6993160247802734
2017/05/25_07:13,Through faith love and resolve the character of the people of Manchester has shown itself. Our thoughts & prayers are with you.https://twitter.com/justinwelby/status/867738559108837377 …,41518,213844,['Manchester' 'GPE'],family,0.67153000831604,positive,0.7116301655769348
2017/05/23_09:56,Our hearts go out to those killed and wounded in Manchester. Americans will always stand shoulder to shoulder with the people of the UK.,212023,1003769,"['Manchester' 'GPE'],['Americans' 'NORP'],['UK' 'GPE']",USA,0.7158228158950806,neutral,0.6371555328369141
2017/05/22_14:16,Excited to hear from Sierra Imani Filiz and Benedikt who are making a difference at home and abroad. See you in Berlin!https://twitter.com/obamafoundation/status/866758362658111488 …,9589,81942,"['Sierra Imani Filiz' 'PERSON'],['Benedikt' 'PERSON']",family,0.5049564838409424,positive,0.9745294451713562
2017/05/14_07:01,Happy Mother's Day to my love and partner on this journey @MichelleObama and to all the wonderful hardworking mothers out there.,107600,714375,['@MichelleObama' 'PERSON'],family,0.8543007373809814,positive,0.9847012758255005
2017/05/02_10:19,Well said Jimmy. That's exactly why we fought so hard for the ACA and why we need to protect it for kids like Billy. And congratulations!https://twitter.com/jimmykimmel/status/859253161873125376 …,124681,491777,"['Jimmy' 'PERSON'],['ACA' 'LAW'],['Billy' 'PERSON']",health,0.7375734448432922,positive,0.8681468367576599
2017/03/23_06:00,My heart goes out to the victims and their families in London. No act of terror can shake the strength and resilience of our British ally.,137843,792156,"['London' 'GPE'],['British' 'NORP']",family,0.723834753036499,neutral,0.4757809042930603
2017/03/19_08:51,Chuck Berry rolled over everyone who came before him – and turned up everyone who came after. We'll miss you Chuck. Be good.,64780,393298,"['Chuck Berry' 'PERSON'],['Chuck' 'PERSON']",family,0.7356244325637817,positive,0.5452244281768799
2017/03/08_13:14,On International Women’s Day @MichelleObama and I are inspired by all of you who embrace your power to drive change.https://twitter.com/obamafoundation/status/839584161442775040 …,49983,267669,['@MichelleObama' 'PERSON'],family,0.5053309202194214,positive,0.9015650749206543
2017/03/02_07:22,Humbled to be recognized by a family with a legacy of service. Who's your #ProfileInCourage? Tell me about them: https://www.obama.org/your-voice/ https://twitter.com/JFKLibrary/status/837318374233354248 …,17938,103628,,family,0.9520169496536255,positive,0.9090957045555115
2017/02/14_07:34,Happy Valentine’s Day @michelleobama! Almost 28 years with you but it always feels new.pic.twitter.com/O0UhJWoqGN,247917,1073972,['@michelleobama' 'PERSON'],family,0.7908483147621155,positive,0.9858773946762085
2016/11/05_08:38,In the weekly address President Obama discusses what #Obamacare has done to improve health care.http://ofa.bo/2ebbyAo,4369,28289,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['Obamacare' 'WORK_OF_ART']",health,0.8803087472915649,neutral,0.7451873421669006
2016/11/04_15:16,Let's keep working to keep our economy on a better stronger course.pic.twitter.com/bV2BVjyj7a,8993,44928,,business,0.4416329562664032,positive,0.8542428016662598
2016/11/04_11:25,The landmark #ParisAgreement enters into force today—we must keep up the momentum to #ActOnClimate. http://ofa.bo/2fn8oHC,5849,24654,['#ParisAgreement' 'LAW'],climate change,0.9205846190452576,positive,0.5430033206939697
2016/11/04_09:12,The economy added 161000 jobs in October and wages are up 2.8 percent over the past year. http://ofa.bo/2e8XF5N  #JobsReport,3759,17189,,business,0.3920227587223053,positive,0.7448737025260925
2016/11/03_12:08,The positive impact of #Obamacare is undeniable but there's one big factor holding many states back:http://ofa.bo/2feEipF,1838,11124,['Obamacare' 'EVENT'],health,0.8734095096588135,positive,0.5078799724578857
2016/11/02_11:22,Tens of millions of Americans have benefited from #Obamacare. Make sure you're one of them. #GetCoveredpic.twitter.com/e1KoXcPtpU,2139,11563,"['Americans' 'NORP'],['Obamacare' 'EVENT']",health,0.7080631852149963,positive,0.7022508978843689
2016/11/02_08:13,Thanks to #Obamacare quality health care is available to everyone. The marketplace is now open—make sure you and your family #GetCovered.pic.twitter.com/0DDAhckcDW,3088,14308,['#Obamacare' 'LAW'],health,0.7595811486244202,positive,0.91351318359375
2016/11/01_10:55,With #Obamacare people can focus on treatment for pre-existing conditions without the fear of coverage being capped or denied. #GetCoveredpic.twitter.com/QqCs6K3y2v,2186,10186,['#Obamacare' 'LAW'],health,0.8482000827789307,neutral,0.6567688584327698
2016/11/01_08:54,The Obamacare marketplace is now open. If you're uninsured now is the time to shop for a plan and #GetCovered. http://ofa.bo/2f9F877 pic.twitter.com/uiA1EGZylU,1075,5523,['Obamacare' 'ORG'],health,0.6691563129425049,neutral,0.7292287945747375
2016/10/31_15:09,Lions and Tiggers and bears! Oh my! #HappyHalloweenpic.twitter.com/iU4fjBhi0Y,6561,32633,,family,0.6180909872055054,positive,0.970401406288147
2016/10/31_13:12,Usted y su familia merecen la tranquilidad de saber que están cubiertos. El mercado de seguros abre mañana.pic.twitter.com/9iRCkLRGZD,969,5254,['Usted' 'PERSON'],family,0.8781749606132507,neutral,0.8346666693687439
2016/10/31_11:08,Speak up in support of quality affordable health care for all.http://ofa.bo/2f5XyoV,958,4975,,health,0.9313919544219971,positive,0.648080587387085
2016/10/31_10:00,There's nothing to be scared of when searching for health insurance. Three in four people can #GetCovered for less than $75 a month.pic.twitter.com/YixI8RXOdq,1666,7288,,health,0.7811998128890991,neutral,0.5085787773132324
2016/10/28_09:50,Senate leaders' obstruction of our Supreme Court nomination process is unacceptable. Say so: http://ofa.bo/2dP8GJo  #DoYourJob,1342,5430,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",business,0.43019869923591614,negative,0.7136837244033813
2016/10/28_08:07,Senate leaders should put the common good above politics—the integrity of our nation's highest court depends on it. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/Ie5vbg4f5D,3585,12797,['Senate' 'ORG'],politics,0.7660970091819763,neutral,0.6367694735527039
2016/10/27_15:17,Don't ghost on your health and well-being—your chance to #GetCovered is coming up. Open enrollment starts November 1.pic.twitter.com/J86AESUreZ,1225,6083,,health,0.9196404218673706,positive,0.5234549045562744
2016/10/27_14:31,Climate change is happening now. Denial is dangerous.http://ofa.bo/2efZv0y,4213,10491,,climate change,0.944085955619812,negative,0.7936580181121826
2016/10/27_13:24,If you're willing to work hard and play by the rules you should be able to get ahead.pic.twitter.com/394hdJttgO,1922,8289,,business,0.39758333563804626,positive,0.6039485931396484
2016/10/27_08:27,Obamacare has helped millions of Americans gain the peace of mind that comes with coverage. Show your support: http://ofa.bo/2dLT09T,1060,4924,"['Obamacare' 'ORG'],['Americans' 'NORP']",health,0.8510572910308838,positive,0.7962985634803772
2016/10/26_12:32,This is what happens when we focus on building an economy that works for everyone not just those at the top.http://ofa.bo/2f890nF,2094,6942,,business,0.4299604296684265,positive,0.5651952028274536
2016/10/25_12:55,Women the sick survivors—they all deserve fair treatment in our health care system. #Obamacarepic.twitter.com/G948HN7pzV,2181,9342,,health,0.8950883150100708,neutral,0.5649823546409607
2016/10/24_14:32,Strong policies that help working families get ahead are good for our economy.pic.twitter.com/QRRhibjZCl,1735,6885,,family,0.6760867238044739,positive,0.9001978635787964
2016/10/24_11:52,Since 2010 America's uninsured rate has been cut in half. Help build on that progress—join Team #Obamacare today: http://ofa.bo/2e4wfdd,735,3397,"['America' 'GPE'],['#Obamacare' 'EVENT']",health,0.610960841178894,positive,0.5673133134841919
2016/10/24_08:21,Health care is a right not a privilege—and #Obamacare works to protect that right for millions of Americans.pic.twitter.com/B7fO8rhggW,2667,11113,['Obamacare' 'ORG'],health,0.9461349844932556,positive,0.541098952293396
2016/10/21_09:40,Being able to stay on a parent's plan enables millions of young adults to make choices about their future with the security of health care.pic.twitter.com/s87tsEpUv1,2467,11726,,health,0.7134184241294861,positive,0.786363959312439
2016/10/21_07:55,Because of Obamacare another 20 million Americans now know the financial security of health insurance.http://www.snappytv.com/tc/3055928,1634,7523,"['Obamacare' 'EVENT'],['Americans' 'NORP']",health,0.7729003429412842,neutral,0.6863739490509033
2016/10/20_13:42,Stand up for the law that's helped 20 million more Americans gain health coverage. Join Team @Obamacare today: http://ofa.bo/2enxsPd,987,4521,['Americans' 'NORP'],health,0.7403889298439026,positive,0.6181420087814331
2016/10/20_10:52,LIVE: President Obama is in Miami talking about the progress made possible by the Affordable Care Act. http://ofa.bo/2ekISnP,582,2701,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['Miami' 'GPE'],['the Affordable Care Act' 'LAW']",health,0.7568767070770264,neutral,0.6857616305351257
2016/10/20_09:54,Tune in at 1:55 p.m. ET to watch President Obama speak about the successes of the Affordable Care Act. http://ofa.bo/2ekISnP,475,2328,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['the Affordable Care Act' 'LAW']",health,0.6554558873176575,positive,0.5541686415672302
2016/10/19_11:07,Our Supreme Court has been short a justice for far too long. #DoYourJob Senate leaders. http://ofa.bo/2e1Kwce,1325,4317,"['Our Supreme Court' 'ORG'],['Senate' 'ORG']",USA,0.4224415123462677,negative,0.5136145353317261
2016/10/18_13:00,We can't afford to let this be the new normal. http://ofa.bo/2dZi76F  #ActOnClimate,1818,4431,,climate change,0.6940982937812805,negative,0.7519808411598206
2016/10/18_11:25,Denying climate change is dangerous. Join @OFA supporters in standing up for bold action now: http://ofa.bo/2e3fRg6  #ActOnClimate,709,2878,['@OFA' 'ORG'],climate change,0.8798128962516785,neutral,0.5053113698959351
2016/10/18_10:10,Climate change is real but so is the progress we're making to #ActOnClimate. Let's keep it up.pic.twitter.com/GOFKXQblGJ,2015,8065,,climate change,0.8990585803985596,positive,0.6978654265403748
2016/10/18_08:45,This is just the latest step forward in the push to #ActOnClimate.http://ofa.bo/2eBOxHu,809,3358,,climate change,0.9100827574729919,positive,0.791650116443634
2016/10/17_14:07,"Wildfires in the next few decades could be ""unrecognizable"" to previous generations—because of climate change:http://ofa.bo/2dWNyOS",1169,3222,,climate change,0.9697244167327881,negative,0.5951533317565918
2016/10/17_11:46,Senate leaders are blocking the Supreme Court nomination for their own political gain—don't be silent: http://ofa.bo/2dJghVG  #DoYourJob,1350,3783,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.9464455842971802,neutral,0.4938373565673828
2016/10/14_14:17,We need a fully functional Supreme Court. Editorial boards across the country agree: http://ofa.bo/2dCG7KU  #DoYourJob,1036,3713,['Supreme Court' 'ORG'],USA,0.42636173963546753,neutral,0.6392314434051514
2016/10/14_12:20,The American Bar Association gave Judge Garland its highest rating. Senate leaders: #DoYourJob and fill the #SCOTUS vacancy.pic.twitter.com/4yseqnOBX4,5298,13682,"['The American Bar Association' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON'],['Senate' 'ORG'],['SCOTUS' 'ORG']",business,0.4211287498474121,neutral,0.5730662941932678
2016/10/14_10:31,Denying climate change is dangerous. Join @OFA supporters in standing up for bold action now: http://ofa.bo/2dZNTRx  #ActOnClimate,711,2768,['@OFA' 'ORG'],climate change,0.8749900460243225,neutral,0.5097644925117493
2016/10/14_09:18,Cynics take note: When we #ActOnClimate we build a stronger future.pic.twitter.com/wHHMdo2ro6,1085,4168,,climate change,0.9248082637786865,positive,0.732243001461029
2016/10/13_13:29,Check out the most recent editorial boards calling on Senate leaders to vote on Judge Garland: http://ofa.bo/2dNKl4h  #DoYourJob,736,2614,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5247491002082825,neutral,0.8363874554634094
2016/10/13_11:29,Senate leaders have undercut the functionality of the Supreme Court and that's unacceptable. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/5HFXhgTMoP,2516,8709,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['the Supreme Court' 'ORG']",business,0.42694514989852905,negative,0.8261417150497437
2016/10/13_09:53,Senate leaders' political games are handicapping the Supreme Court—and judgeships across the country. http://ofa.bo/2dVVHno  #DoYourJob,1041,3196,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['the Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.828053891658783,negative,0.5623347759246826
2016/10/12_12:43,Support the bold steps we're taking against climate change. Say you're ready to #ActOnClimate: http://ofa.bo/2dcUwww,554,2281,['#ActOnClimate:' 'EVENT'],climate change,0.9056468605995178,positive,0.5714442729949951
2016/10/12_10:57,Last week more than 190 countries reached a landmark deal to reduce carbon pollution from aviation. http://ofa.bo/2dcG2Nb  #ActOnClimate,897,3564,,climate change,0.7077499628067017,positive,0.6792299151420593
2016/10/12_08:25,Climate change's effects are devastating. Denying the science behind it does nothing to help. http://ofa.bo/2d7ppaq  #ActOnClimate,1239,3444,,climate change,0.9262657165527344,negative,0.8413189649581909
2016/10/11_16:59,On behalf of Michelle and our family G’mar Chatimah Tovah.  #YomKippur,1616,7334,['Michelle' 'PERSON'],family,0.9684175848960876,neutral,0.8141648769378662
2016/10/11_13:02,The Supreme Court must remain above politics. Judge Garland needs a hearing and a vote. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/eVSPSIFNpB,3048,9970,"['The Supreme Court' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5014147162437439,neutral,0.7016196250915527
2016/10/07_15:03,The uninsured rate is the lowest it's been in decades thanks to #Obamacare. Spread the word. http://ofa.bo/2dLpd09 pic.twitter.com/zH364SozNu,1768,6526,,health,0.7634168267250061,positive,0.7265214920043945
2016/10/07_13:38,Deadline tonight—help rein in payday lenders that succeed by targeting vulnerable Americans: http://ofa.bo/2cXFmzM  #StopTheDebtTrap,650,2334,['Americans' 'NORP'],finance,0.6771500110626221,neutral,0.6821441650390625
2016/10/07_12:54,The Obama administration and @CFPB are working to protect consumers and #StopTheDebtTrap.pic.twitter.com/UMO01OUkdh,588,2543,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@CFPB' 'ORG']",finance,0.5940893292427063,neutral,0.5894359350204468
2016/10/07_11:02,Our economy is on a better stronger course.http://ofa.bo/2dkzDAj,609,2548,,business,0.5228713154792786,positive,0.9029539227485657
2016/10/07_09:16,The economic progress we've made is undeniable—let's keep it up.pic.twitter.com/gAlfaC1hkI,1098,3795,,business,0.5983430743217468,positive,0.9454753398895264
2016/10/07_08:14,Check out President Obama's essay in @TheEconomist on the unique challenges the American economy faces.http://ofa.bo/2dk8Ynm,1168,3294,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@TheEconomist' 'WORK_OF_ART'],['American' 'NORP']",USA,0.7272195219993591,neutral,0.7567534446716309
2016/10/06_11:35,ICYMI: Read about the historic #ParisAgreement and what it means for the fight to #ActOnClimate.http://ofa.bo/2dyb5WA,752,2688,['#ParisAgreement' 'LAW'],climate change,0.8741030097007751,neutral,0.8116750717163086
2016/10/05_14:30,This historic step in the fight to #ActOnClimate came faster than anyone predicted.pic.twitter.com/W2rtcNXkI7,1314,5413,,climate change,0.9487174153327942,positive,0.8910635113716125
2016/10/05_13:44,Today is a historic day in the fight to protect our planet for future generations.  #ActOnClimatehttp://www.snappytv.com/tc/2949825,1726,6008,,climate change,0.7182325720787048,positive,0.8606497645378113
2016/10/05_12:30,LIVE: President Obama is delivering a statement on the Paris Climate Agreement. http://ofa.bo/2dFlmSh,481,1876,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['the Paris Climate Agreement' 'LAW']",climate change,0.7099192142486572,neutral,0.8231951594352722
2016/10/05_08:50,Read from @NYTopinion about why filling the Supreme Court vacancy is crucial for our democracy: http://ofa.bo/2dEKeJE  #DoYourJob,750,2391,"['@NYTopinion' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.6865566372871399,neutral,0.7492053508758545
2016/10/04_13:30,Enough is enough. Say it's time for Senate leaders to get to work: http://ofa.bo/2dtojUl  #DoYourJob,671,2632,['Senate' 'ORG'],business,0.5673269629478455,neutral,0.5949206948280334
2016/10/04_11:28,Everybody cares about their kids their grandkids and the kind of world we pass on to them. http://www.snappytv.com/tc/2936623,1965,6891,,family,0.918555736541748,neutral,0.5859392881393433
2016/09/30_13:11,After thirty years in Congress Senator this should not be your proudest accomplishment. http://ofa.bo/2dBY0hA  #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/TIL8ISwdKd,2032,5162,['Congress' 'ORG'],politics,0.5072609782218933,negative,0.628301203250885
2016/09/30_08:57,There has never been a more qualified nominee Senate leaders. He deserves a fair hearing and a vote. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/qtzcY3iwyl,3085,9585,['Senate' 'ORG'],business,0.4042791426181793,positive,0.576947808265686
2016/09/29_14:55,It's the Senate's job to fairly consider Supreme Court nominees. Their refusal to do so is unacceptable: http://ofa.bo/2cZAI0q  #DoYourJob,1056,3526,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",business,0.4503284692764282,negative,0.6820403933525085
2016/09/29_12:41,Everybody gets sick. Check out what President Obama is doing to extend access to paid sick leave: http://ofa.bo/2cEHvAx  #LeadOnLeave,655,2788,['Obama' 'PERSON'],health,0.7052147388458252,neutral,0.5931547284126282
2016/09/29_09:33,Never underestimate the strength and resilience of the American economy.pic.twitter.com/OFTN2FlRtq,1326,5385,['American' 'NORP'],USA,0.8935225009918213,positive,0.6372376680374146
2016/09/28_08:16,This is no accident—we're making a comeback because together we've fought hard to support American families.pic.twitter.com/LTk7SiTexP,3042,10668,['American' 'NORP'],family,0.7237457633018494,positive,0.8539278507232666
2016/09/27_09:57,As long as Senate leaders keep refusing to do their jobs @OFA supporters will continue speaking out against their obstruction. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/xrz67jh1HV,2786,8228,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['@OFA' 'ORG']",business,0.4471731185913086,negative,0.6393497586250305
2016/09/27_08:28,Senate leaders have blocked Judge Garland's hearing for over six months now. Keep pushing: http://ofa.bo/2d6yD5J  #DoYourJob,835,2689,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5633682012557983,negative,0.5644831657409668
2016/09/26_11:59,These are high praises from the American Bar Association—and yet Senate leaders refuse to even consider Judge Garland. #MerricksMeritspic.twitter.com/tXakoNmYFu,2301,7157,"['the American Bar Association' 'ORG'],['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.7131021022796631,negative,0.5889869928359985
2016/09/23_14:12,Senate leaders have blocked Judge Garland's hearing for over six months now. Keep pushing: http://ofa.bo/2cJwSYX  #DoYourJob,778,2396,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5386308431625366,negative,0.5710318088531494
2016/09/23_12:03,Watch President Obama and @CEAChair Jason Furman discuss the positive gains the American economy has made.http://ofa.bo/2ctwCBa,463,1662,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@CEAChair' 'ORG'],['Jason Furman' 'PERSON'],['American' 'NORP']",USA,0.41710934042930603,positive,0.6069294214248657
2016/09/23_08:57,Another record broken: 16 months in a row of undeniable record-breaking heat. http://ofa.bo/2dabz7s  #ActOnClimate,1386,2629,,climate change,0.7934749722480774,neutral,0.564225971698761
2016/09/22_14:21,We can't sit idly by. Climate change is likely to threaten our national security—we must act now. http://ofa.bo/2crGwUg  #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/CCFZdEYc8T,1511,4926,,climate change,0.9291062355041504,negative,0.6962029933929443
2016/09/22_10:34,Senate leaders' blind obstruction of Judge Garland's nomination sets a dangerous precedent. We can't stand idly by. http://ofa.bo/2d4dlEi,766,2414,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",business,0.4275169372558594,negative,0.7111544609069824
2016/09/22_08:58,Enough of the shameless partisanship Senators. #DoYourJob and fill the Supreme Court vacancy.pic.twitter.com/vIQY0bivo4,2255,6373,['Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.7348212599754333,negative,0.5964755415916443
2016/09/21_10:53,The American Bar Association gave Judge Garland its highest possible rating. He deserves a hearing and a vote. #MerricksMeritspic.twitter.com/ItMNKx4RJx,3075,9119,"['The American Bar Association' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",USA,0.42804765701293945,positive,0.7526435852050781
2016/09/21_07:57,Communities are already experiencing the effects of climate change—we can't afford not to act. Take a look: http://ofa.bo/2d1OQbb pic.twitter.com/3BFbRDUXBv,1752,5446,,climate change,0.8950557708740234,neutral,0.4994840621948242
2016/09/20_12:31,As the #UNGA meets take a look at the progress we've made thanks to American leadership in the world.http://ofa.bo/2cX9zhF,851,3599,"['UNGA' 'ORG'],['American' 'NORP']",USA,0.8968098759651184,positive,0.5301706790924072
2016/09/16_14:23,Senate leaders are putting politics above their basic responsibility to hold a hearing for Judge Garland. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/N7vH2ncwmb,3423,7958,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.9175402522087097,neutral,0.5213920474052429
2016/09/16_12:55,Six months is long enough senators. It's time to #DoYourJob and give Judge Garland a hearing. http://ofa.bo/2csXei1,954,3061,['Garland' 'PERSON'],business,0.5746843814849854,neutral,0.6353186964988708
2016/09/15_11:51,There is no 'election year' exception in Article II. Sen. Leahy calls on senators to give Judge Garland a hearing:http://ofa.bo/2cb8DBX,1295,3972,"['Article II' 'LAW'],['Leahy' 'PERSON'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.576097309589386,neutral,0.7737681865692139
2016/09/15_09:39,President Obama just made history by protecting nearly 5000 square miles off the New England coast. http://ofa.bo/2caUhRY  #OurOcean,2426,6699,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['nearly 5000 square miles' 'QUANTITY'],['New England' 'LOC']",USA,0.5036727786064148,positive,0.6042237281799316
2016/09/15_08:15,LIVE: President Obama is speaking at the 2016 Our Ocean Conference. http://ofa.bo/2cQJ3DM  #OurOcean,418,1718,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['Our Ocean Conference' 'EVENT']",USA,0.43165093660354614,neutral,0.8321913480758667
2016/09/14_13:45,We need nine justices for a fully functioning Supreme Court—and editorial boards across the country agree. http://ofa.bo/2c9hILF,1475,4649,['Supreme Court' 'ORG'],USA,0.44626760482788086,neutral,0.7036297917366028
2016/09/14_10:50,We can't let Senate leaders ignore their constitutional responsibilities. http://ofa.bo/2cIlvVN  #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/IwO7CAoVm2,1482,4085,['Senate' 'ORG'],business,0.4635471701622009,negative,0.5319633483886719
2016/09/14_08:24,The U.S. is on track to hit two million solar installations within the next two years. Momentum is building:http://ofa.bo/2caExn4,1704,5734,['U.S.' 'GPE'],USA,0.8357090950012207,neutral,0.5068715810775757
2016/09/13_14:14,Time is almost up for Senate leaders to do the right thing and fill the #SCOTUS vacancy. http://ofa.bo/2cpD3Ct  #DoYourJob,611,2132,['Senate' 'ORG'],politics,0.5526362061500549,neutral,0.656207263469696
2016/09/12_11:55,"Vice President Biden speaks on the ""dangerous precedent"" Senate leaders are setting by refusing to do their jobs.http://ofa.bo/2cjizdw",1572,4783,"['Biden' 'PERSON'],['Senate' 'ORG']",politics,0.6188305616378784,negative,0.5598562359809875
2016/09/12_10:36,These are records we can't keep breaking. We must work together to #ActOnClimate.pic.twitter.com/sTxNR10sjK,2962,6133,,climate change,0.8452782034873962,neutral,0.561867892742157
2016/09/12_08:09,Meaningful action on climate change can't wait. President Obama explains why in this @nytimes interview.http://ofa.bo/2cH9trK,1269,4033,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@nytimes' 'ORG']",climate change,0.937349796295166,positive,0.5349529981613159
2016/09/09_14:05,We need to keep up efforts to fight climate change at every level—locally nationally globally. #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/L10qdkgPDg,3467,10061,,climate change,0.9309783577919006,neutral,0.6167276501655579
2016/09/09_10:47,There's no need to overcomplicate the process. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/QgaNgKNBzJ,1295,3543,,business,0.5630837678909302,neutral,0.6513732075691223
2016/09/09_08:08,We must take bold steps now—climate change is already impacting millions of people. http://ofa.bo/2czxiBK  #ActOnClimate,1308,3817,,climate change,0.940463662147522,neutral,0.5997397303581238
2016/09/08_12:39,Congress is back and they have important work to do before their next recess. Make sure you say where you stand: http://ofa.bo/2co9UcY,914,3308,['Congress' 'ORG'],business,0.8417035341262817,neutral,0.7310068607330322
2016/09/07_14:47,Rising sea levels are already flooding homes and roads along America's coasts. The time to #ActOnClimate is now.http://ofa.bo/2bUKt3i,1759,4334,"['America' 'GPE'],['#ActOnClimate is' 'WORK_OF_ART']",climate change,0.7390135526657104,negative,0.48498454689979553
2016/09/07_13:00,Fewer Americans are uninsured than ever before thanks to #Obamacare.http://ofa.bo/2cilNlT,812,2915,['Americans' 'NORP'],health,0.6509933471679688,neutral,0.5381342172622681
2016/09/07_10:48,Congress is back from recess. Help put the pressure on Senate leaders to give Judge Garland a hearing: http://ofa.bo/2ckGIU7  #DoYourJob,807,2670,"['Congress' 'ORG'],['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",business,0.3986879885196686,neutral,0.8186259865760803
2016/09/06_14:57,Senate leaders have 32 days before their next recess to give Judge Garland a hearing and a vote. Call them out now: http://ofa.bo/2chZqvI,1025,3099,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5088878273963928,neutral,0.8299776911735535
2016/09/06_13:19,The Paris Climate Agreement is a big deal in the fight against climate change—and now a big step closer to reality.http://ofa.bo/2c20UYS,1162,3706,['The Paris Climate Agreement' 'LAW'],climate change,0.8578040599822998,positive,0.7394413948059082
2016/09/06_11:57,The United States is leading the way in the fight to #ActOnClimate.pic.twitter.com/vkUMjg6XKc,587,2375,['The United States' 'GPE'],USA,0.7577210068702698,positive,0.6352908611297607
2016/09/06_09:58,Conservation not only protects diverse lands and species it's also an important part of battling climate change.http://ofa.bo/2c1ui1v,1184,4064,,climate change,0.7656559348106384,positive,0.49180564284324646
2016/09/06_08:03,When we protect our lands it helps us protect the climate for the future.  #ActOnClimatehttp://www.snappytv.com/tc/2710336,1244,4510,,climate change,0.7085984349250793,positive,0.580357015132904
2016/09/05_09:03,President Obama has a message for America's workers today—check it out: http://ofa.bo/2c9zC6j  #LaborDaypic.twitter.com/qzbHAfRXNs,866,3737,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['America' 'GPE']",USA,0.603971540927887,neutral,0.760905385017395
2016/09/03_10:01,In the weekly address President Obama commemorates the labor movement that helped build this country.http://ofa.bo/2bY9ruQ,1095,4673,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.6417807936668396,positive,0.6901991963386536
2016/09/02_15:27,Recess is almost over and editorial boards across the country are calling for Senate leaders to do their jobs.pic.twitter.com/Pr78WaT0V2,2465,7684,['Senate' 'ORG'],politics,0.4984116852283478,neutral,0.7421860694885254
2016/09/02_11:28,Unemployment: Deficits: Uninsured rate: Jobs: +15.1 millionpic.twitter.com/mWcAgfM8zn,2597,8120,,finance,0.42293021082878113,neutral,0.573655366897583
2016/09/01_14:06,Senate leaders return from recess next week. They need to get to work on a vote for Judge Garland—say so. http://ofa.bo/2bUhngC  #DoYourJob,850,3044,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",business,0.7824550867080688,neutral,0.7932575941085815
2016/09/01_12:33,Recess is almost over and editorial boards across the country are calling for Senate leaders to do their jobs.pic.twitter.com/ScbkMVcovu,2647,8843,['Senate' 'ORG'],politics,0.48345544934272766,neutral,0.7390583157539368
2016/08/31_12:42,Senate leaders need to hear you expect a vote on Judge Garland when recess ends—say you'll let them know: http://ofa.bo/2bCovlE  #DoYourJob,770,2759,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",business,0.7152643203735352,neutral,0.8159956336021423
2016/08/31_09:24,The American people need their legislators to be dedicated to solutions not obstruction. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/mrTXe8sti6,3006,7469,['American' 'NORP'],USA,0.48073112964630127,neutral,0.6185653209686279
2016/08/30_15:17,Senate leaders have a job to do—join the thousands reminding them when they reconvene next week. http://ofa.bo/2bA3t72  #DoYourJob,736,2605,['Senate' 'ORG'],business,0.6517009139060974,neutral,0.7169520258903503
2016/08/30_13:03,Summer's almost over Senate leaders. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/JOEchACJ6i,2147,5929,['Senate' 'ORG'],business,0.5704679489135742,neutral,0.6508579254150391
2016/08/29_14:15,Senate leaders must put country before party politics. Read why it's time to give Judge Garland a vote. http://ofa.bo/2bMWVm0,1032,3675,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.6150686740875244,neutral,0.7373998761177063
2016/08/29_12:10,It's not too late for Senate leaders to give Judge Garland a fair hearing and up-or-down vote. Say you agree. http://ofa.bo/2bx2xjL,1352,4729,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.4748961329460144,neutral,0.674949049949646
2016/08/26_11:45,Say you'll continue the fight to make gender equality a reality in America: http://ofa.bo/2cfsWE1  #WomensEqualityDay,711,2348,['America' 'GPE'],USA,0.8790035843849182,neutral,0.6944944262504578
2016/08/25_15:13,These are our American cathedrals and they belong to you. —Jonathan B. Jarvis director of the @NatlParkServicehttp://ofa.bo/2bJTZFC,1434,5148,"['American' 'NORP'],['Jonathan B. Jarvis' 'PERSON']",USA,0.8206952810287476,neutral,0.7793939709663391
2016/08/24_13:32,This is nothing more than shameless partisanship. The Supreme Court should be held in higher regard. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/I0TN3csv0O,3963,9913,['The Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.9256740808486938,negative,0.6276367902755737
2016/08/24_08:17,America's leadership in the fight against climate change pays off in more ways than one. #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/tGK9Uu5l0C,1525,6078,['America' 'GPE'],USA,0.8443595767021179,positive,0.6308385133743286
2016/08/22_10:45,Read why the Supreme Court needs nine justices not shameless partisanship. http://ofa.bo/2bAC2ZS,847,2849,['the Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.7087785601615906,neutral,0.5990618467330933
2016/08/20_09:04,In the weekly address President Obama commemorates the 100th anniversary of the @NatlParkService. http://ofa.bo/2bEPI3X,772,3902,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.5237628817558289,neutral,0.5540513396263123
2016/08/19_10:14,Our children's health and prosperity is too important to ignore the consequences of climate change. Speak out now: http://ofa.bo/2bsKGtH,780,2768,,climate change,0.8522987365722656,neutral,0.48056885600090027
2016/08/19_08:17,Climate change is not too big of a challenge to solve. We're making good headway. #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/s2yzyDqvNR,2004,8332,,climate change,0.9620927572250366,positive,0.896787703037262
2016/08/18_14:59,“Each month just gives another data point that makes the evidence stronger that we’re changing the climate.”http://ofa.bo/2bqW74M,2960,5904,,climate change,0.9601085186004639,positive,0.7237464189529419
2016/08/18_13:57,Fifteen months in a row of record-breaking heat is a signal that can't be denied: We need to #ActOnClimate.pic.twitter.com/pXnbiNYFP9,5051,10729,,climate change,0.903727650642395,positive,0.5266188979148865
2016/08/17_08:39,Doing nothing won't stop our country's gun violence epidemic. Congress must act to #DisarmHate.pic.twitter.com/0kbF22nnm4,4300,14990,['Congress' 'ORG'],business,0.39176857471466064,negative,0.7347009778022766
2016/08/16_11:48,We’re taking important steps to help guarantee the basic security of paid family leave. http://ofa.bo/2bbSEpH  #LeadOnLeave,563,2272,,family,0.8137540817260742,positive,0.7435162663459778
2016/08/16_07:52,Reminder: It's the Senate's job to fairly consider Supreme Court nominees. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/xrkYcRsLNw,2810,9430,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",business,0.5475083589553833,neutral,0.769709050655365
2016/08/15_10:07,It’s not too late. Senate leaders can still make this right and give Judge Garland an up-or-down vote.pic.twitter.com/ysc4UvluR0,2732,8709,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.51472407579422,neutral,0.6133962869644165
2016/08/15_08:31,Editorial boards around the country agree: Our judicial system is too important to be used as a political football. http://ofa.bo/2aUto4q,975,3171,,politics,0.6055288314819336,neutral,0.6135518550872803
2016/08/13_11:56,There's no doubt that America has become a global leader in the fight against climate change. http://ofa.bo/2bdVxaK,1162,5648,['America' 'GPE'],USA,0.7320011258125305,positive,0.8213053345680237
2016/08/13_10:44,In the weekly address President Obama discusses progress made in combating climate change—and what's left to do. http://ofa.bo/2bdVxaK,790,3693,['Obama' 'PERSON'],climate change,0.9138094186782837,neutral,0.727038562297821
2016/08/12_14:55,Let's be clear: Senate leaders are playing political games with the Supreme Court. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/EpPURJ3Dwa,3409,10199,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['the Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.9470374584197998,negative,0.5237390995025635
2016/08/12_11:39,Not long ago women could be charged more for health insurance—for being women. There's more to do: http://ofa.bo/2bbL4wx  #StandWithWomen,636,2511,,health,0.8892868161201477,neutral,0.613412618637085
2016/08/11_14:58,Senate leaders continue to obstruct a full Supreme Court and it must stop—add your name if you agree: http://ofa.bo/2b9zJNr  #DoYourJob,897,2698,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.6818904876708984,negative,0.6508169174194336
2016/08/11_11:51,20 million more insured 15 million new jobs A global climate agreement Let's keep it going:http://ofa.bo/2b1PiW6,961,3829,,climate change,0.7752302289009094,positive,0.7447152137756348
2016/08/10_13:26,Grab one of these for all your progressive organizing travels. http://ofa.bo/2b6Wr8X pic.twitter.com/UlT5Wszne5,370,2143,,politics,0.5608757734298706,neutral,0.7304905652999878
2016/08/09_13:54,Judge Garland has now waited 146 days. That's shameful—and irresponsible. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/JaP7YUQyOV,5374,11888,['Garland' 'PERSON'],business,0.43791663646698,negative,0.88456130027771
2016/08/09_12:01,Senate leaders are hamstringing our Supreme Court. This obstruction is unprecedented—and unacceptable: http://ofa.bo/2b4cPXL  #DoYourJob,1077,3268,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",USA,0.4844338595867157,negative,0.7926087975502014
2016/08/09_09:59,Editorial boards from across the country have called on Senate leaders to fill the Supreme Court vacancy. http://ofa.bo/2axXIq3,1094,3600,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.551452100276947,neutral,0.8635181188583374
2016/08/08_14:00,President Obama has done more to improve energy efficiency than any previous U.S. leader. http://ofa.bo/2b1FGfp  #ActOnClimate,1554,6029,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['U.S.' 'GPE']",USA,0.5488423705101013,positive,0.7639506459236145
2016/08/08_12:41,Adding clean energy jobs is another way the U.S. is continuing to #ActOnClimate.pic.twitter.com/EbM6XUrDRW,943,3725,['U.S.' 'GPE'],USA,0.6729019284248352,positive,0.5936456322669983
2016/08/08_11:13,Show your support for bold action to fight climate change. http://ofa.bo/2b1kV3k  #ActOnClimate,478,1744,,climate change,0.928137481212616,positive,0.6635633111000061
2016/08/08_09:40,Americans across the country agree that we need bold action in the fight against climate change. #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/znuajZ6CmE,1652,7157,['Americans' 'NORP'],climate change,0.624110996723175,neutral,0.5554884076118469
2016/08/08_08:16,These extreme records aren't a fluke—climate change is largely caused by human activity. http://ofa.bo/2azFXCj  #ActOnClimate,1730,3873,,climate change,0.9487016797065735,neutral,0.5027003288269043
2016/08/06_12:17,Team USA reminds the world why America always sets the gold standard. http://ofa.bo/2auHwRO,1724,7962,"['Team USA' 'ORG'],['America' 'GPE']",USA,0.974841296672821,positive,0.6619120240211487
2016/08/05_14:12,President Obama reflects on his experience as a feminist—and his hopes to continue building toward gender equality.http://ofa.bo/2aB6Lrl,3892,13034,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.4207434356212616,neutral,0.7050797343254089
2016/08/05_11:18,Today's jobs report underscores what we know to be true: America's economy is the strongest in the world.pic.twitter.com/iXJjuWeOB6,3095,11511,['America' 'GPE'],USA,0.8725205659866333,positive,0.9173172116279602
2016/08/05_09:49,This is a good thing for American workers and businesses—but there's more work to do.pic.twitter.com/QGb6k0pwPr,1621,5657,['American' 'NORP'],business,0.46021872758865356,positive,0.8146329522132874
2016/08/05_08:42,Our economy is continuing its comeback. Let's keep up the progress.pic.twitter.com/qUPGBzkqQ5,1587,6744,,business,0.5088838338851929,positive,0.9151566028594971
2016/08/05_07:31,The economy added 255000 jobs in July—a record-breaking 77 months of private-sector job growth.,2880,9471,,business,0.3967283368110657,positive,0.8514291048049927
2016/08/04_15:29,It’s President Obama’s last birthday in office—​d​on’t forget to sign ​the card. http://ofa.bo/2ayv2hY,1147,5661,['Obama' 'PERSON'],politics,0.6707099080085754,neutral,0.5101545453071594
2016/08/04_10:46,Make President Obama's last birthday in office extra special. Sign the card: http://ofa.bo/2aTo9WO  #TBTpic.twitter.com/eEqqEJ114i,1670,7773,['Obama' 'PERSON'],politics,0.4908226430416107,positive,0.5386193990707397
2016/08/04_09:22,The Clean Power Plan is one of the biggest steps forward in the fight to #ActOnClimate.pic.twitter.com/UBXPe98NUF,1397,6101,['The Clean Power Plan' 'LAW'],climate change,0.9266926050186157,positive,0.8919504880905151
2016/08/03_14:42,From the Clean Power Plan to the Paris Climate Agreement the U.S. is leading the way in the fight to #ActOnClimate.pic.twitter.com/aBMaZdrgGB,807,3656,"['the Clean Power Plan' 'LAW'],['the Paris Climate Agreement' 'LAW'],['U.S.' 'GPE']",USA,0.6036655902862549,neutral,0.6108635663986206
2016/08/03_11:35,Today is the one-year anniversary of the Clean Power Plan—show your support in the fight to #ActOnClimate. http://ofa.bo/2av5KRJ,569,2193,['the Clean Power Plan' 'LAW'],climate change,0.8329046964645386,positive,0.620772123336792
2016/08/03_10:11,The Clean Power Plan will cut carbon pollution from power plants by 32 percent by 2030. #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/UDp2Ti5ji1,1570,6122,['The Clean Power Plan' 'LAW'],climate change,0.788330614566803,neutral,0.641904354095459
2016/08/02_12:45,Senate leaders are weakening our highest court by refusing to vote on Judge Garland. http://ofa.bo/2ajlr8N  #DoYourJob,738,2469,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5696770548820496,negative,0.6910094022750854
2016/08/02_08:28,44 is turning 55. Celebrate—sign the card. http://ofa.bo/2arQcOz,825,4477,,family,0.5655257701873779,positive,0.8441744446754456
2016/08/01_13:58,Judge Garland should get a fair hearing and an up-or-down vote from the Senate. Speak out. http://ofa.bo/2aDY78a  #DoYourJob,946,3098,"['Garland' 'PERSON'],['Senate' 'ORG']",business,0.3852345943450928,neutral,0.71114182472229
2016/08/01_11:45,The Supreme Court still needs a ninth justice but Senate leaders are still refusing to do their jobs. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/HmgNHkz7e8,7160,16291,"['The Supreme Court' 'ORG'],['Senate' 'ORG']",politics,0.5847680568695068,negative,0.6560242772102356
2016/07/30_10:36,Sign the card and wish President Obama a happy birthday. http://ofa.bo/2azUsdv pic.twitter.com/0dkapeIOjR,1511,7692,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.4148918390274048,positive,0.9208504557609558
2016/07/30_09:39,In the weekly address retired Federal Judge Timothy Lewis joins @VP Biden to discuss the #SCOTUS vacancy.http://ofa.bo/2akk9jJ,452,2132,"['Timothy Lewis' 'PERSON'],['Biden' 'PERSON'],['SCOTUS' 'ORG']",politics,0.7557056546211243,neutral,0.8392331600189209
2016/07/29_13:22,Before their obstruction of President Obama's nominee these six senators voted to confirm Judge Garland.pic.twitter.com/xiGIdD2Ask,3160,7674,['Obama' 'PERSON'],politics,0.5352559089660645,neutral,0.6919233202934265
2016/07/29_12:05,Add your name if you think the Supreme Court is no place for partisan political games: http://ofa.bo/2auVlDO  #DoYourJob,727,2826,['the Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.7019250392913818,negative,0.5712494254112244
2016/07/29_10:42,It's been a record-breaking 135 days since President Obama nominated Judge Garland. The obstruction must end.pic.twitter.com/0P8jRkYUCq,5715,17145,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5389198064804077,neutral,0.5410005450248718
2016/07/28_13:41,Our children's health and prosperity is too important to ignore the consequences of climate change. Speak out now: http://ofa.bo/2afsLYI,872,2976,,climate change,0.8450392484664917,neutral,0.4894607365131378
2016/07/28_12:41,Wildfire seasons are getting longer more dangerous and more expensive. We need to do more to #ActOnClimate.http://ofa.bo/2au2V07,1117,3152,,climate change,0.8252273201942444,negative,0.8096568584442139
2016/07/28_08:31,It's time to offer serious solutions on how to build on #Obamacare's progress—not take it away.pic.twitter.com/rw69A5Jybh,1290,4821,['Obamacare' 'LAW'],health,0.8531519770622253,neutral,0.5864670276641846
2016/07/27_10:24,Thanks to #Obamacare millions of Americans have gained the coverage they need. Say you're proud. http://ofa.bo/2aqDjBj,1107,4674,"['#Obamacare' 'EVENT'],['Americans' 'NORP']",health,0.8595170974731445,positive,0.8670192360877991
2016/07/27_08:38,Six years later and Republican leaders still have no credible #Obamacare alternative.pic.twitter.com/Y6yMqo4bEe,5434,17205,['Republican' 'NORP'],health,0.8082661032676697,negative,0.7139957547187805
2016/07/26_11:36,Let's be clear: #Obamacare is working and helping millions of Americans.pic.twitter.com/OVZqdsjkOn,2076,8010,['Obamacare' 'ORG'],health,0.9250121116638184,positive,0.7999127507209778
2016/07/26_09:25,97 percent of climate scientists agree—climate change is real and man-made. Stand up for bold action: http://ofa.bo/2a8V4rM  #ActOnClimate,1140,3463,,climate change,0.9138997793197632,positive,0.6448819041252136
2016/07/26_08:13,It's easy to be cynical but there's no challenge we can't overcome. #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/OeUW6YqvLc,2775,9547,,climate change,0.8407105207443237,neutral,0.4950028955936432
2016/07/25_13:33,Actively ignoring this epidemic is unacceptable. Congress has to act. #DisarmHatepic.twitter.com/n46r7RDnQI,4765,13792,['Congress' 'ORG'],business,0.5557776689529419,negative,0.7947503328323364
2016/07/25_11:02,Add your name if you believe Senate leaders need to put aside partisan politics and fill the Supreme Court vacancy. http://ofa.bo/2a6q4IP,696,2731,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.7110759019851685,neutral,0.75318443775177
2016/07/25_10:02,Restoring the Supreme Court to full strength must remain above Senate leaders' petty politics. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/H5EWm5gQug,3728,11115,"['the Supreme Court' 'ORG'],['Senate' 'ORG']",politics,0.7027588486671448,neutral,0.7112889289855957
2016/07/25_08:55,The federal minimum wage hasn't been raised since 2009. $7.25 isn't enough to make ends meet—we need to #RaiseTheWage.,3437,9712,,finance,0.6146345138549805,negative,0.7373270988464355
2016/07/23_09:08,In the weekly address @SenWarren joins President Obama to discuss economic progress and Wall Street reform. http://ofa.bo/2a8qop4,608,2696,['Obama' 'PERSON'],finance,0.5264793634414673,neutral,0.8456985950469971
2016/07/22_09:41,Add your name if you believe Senate leaders need to put aside partisan politics and fill the Supreme Court vacancy: http://ofa.bo/2aek4uj,988,3435,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.7605451941490173,neutral,0.7606251835823059
2016/07/22_08:23,A reminder for Senate leaders: Judge Garland has had strong bipartisan support in the past. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/dFjboU0TYX,3253,9201,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",business,0.49514737725257874,neutral,0.5334236025810242
2016/07/21_12:13,Our economy is making real progress.pic.twitter.com/xBgqyYEoG0,2475,8695,,business,0.562676191329956,positive,0.9300715327262878
2016/07/21_08:59,America’s businesses have created more than 14 million new private-sector jobs over 76 straight months.pic.twitter.com/e4a5X2bv0j,4432,15388,['America' 'GPE'],business,0.6649906039237976,positive,0.7089617252349854
2016/07/20_12:34,For three years in a row heat records have been broken across the globe. We have to #ActOnClimate now.http://ofa.bo/29VhPcv,1651,3923,['#ActOnClimate' 'WORK_OF_ART'],climate change,0.9369474649429321,neutral,0.46806788444519043
2016/07/20_08:38,Make your voice heard: The Senate must fill the vacancy on the Supreme Court. http://ofa.bo/b6Ix  #DoYourJob,1013,2830,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['the Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.5095965266227722,neutral,0.762392520904541
2016/07/18_13:43,Editorial boards across the country are calling on Senate leaders to fill the Supreme Court vacancy. Read more: http://ofa.bo/ugu ,1109,3197,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.5321931838989258,neutral,0.8492053747177124
2016/07/18_09:42,Read President Obama's op-ed in the @WSJ on the need for Senate leaders to fill the #SCOTUS vacancy: http://ofa.bo/jAPj  #DoYourJob,902,2516,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@WSJ' 'ORG'],['Senate' 'ORG'],['SCOTUS' 'ORG']",politics,0.6334071755409241,neutral,0.8036305904388428
2016/07/14_14:28,Tonight: President Obama joins a town hall discussion on communities and policing. Watch at 8 p.m. ET on @ABC: http://ofa.bo/b6IY,801,3099,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@ABC' 'ORG']",politics,0.5421611070632935,neutral,0.8682922720909119
2016/07/14_09:27,Check out @VP Biden on the Supreme Court vacancy and Senate Republicans’ continued obstruction. http://ofa.bo/iATs  #DoYourJob,575,2265,"['Biden' 'PERSON'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG'],['Senate' 'ORG'],['Republicans' 'NORP']",politics,0.7586450576782227,neutral,0.6364246606826782
2016/07/12_11:47,President Obama is delivering remarks at an interfaith memorial service for the fallen police officers in Dallas. http://ofa.bo/c6Bk,803,3319,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['Dallas' 'GPE']",USA,0.43577882647514343,neutral,0.8510853052139282
2016/07/01_12:17,Chicago raising its minimum wage is another reminder: Congress needs to keep up and #RaiseTheWage for hard-working Americans nationwide.,1384,5722,"['Chicago' 'GPE'],['Congress' 'ORG'],['Americans' 'NORP']",finance,0.4230758249759674,neutral,0.7073547840118408
2016/07/01_08:55,Since #Obamacare passed health care spending has been slowing—and the uninsured rate is down to an all-time low.http://ofa.bo/xbU ,1171,3391,['#Obamacare passed' 'EVENT'],health,0.8721232414245605,neutral,0.5501515865325928
2016/06/30_14:54,Stretch it out and get ready—the fundraising deadline is tonight. http://ofa.bo/gAL8 pic.twitter.com/rwNuTtdgKA,1057,5766,,business,0.4070329964160919,neutral,0.8542718887329102
2016/06/30_12:29,An overwhelming majority of Americans agree—Congress needs to act. #DisarmHatepic.twitter.com/JuVv8MrEaO,2546,9238,"['Americans' 'NORP'],['Congress' 'ORG']",USA,0.4656096398830414,neutral,0.6177428960800171
2016/06/29_15:30,Add your name if you agree: Climate change is real and it's going to take global action to tackle it. http://ofa.bo/uav  #ActOnClimate,849,2970,,climate change,0.8273387551307678,neutral,0.6403926014900208
2016/06/29_14:17,A new historic goal in the fight to #ActOnClimate.pic.twitter.com/sAu2fHdxAb,1364,5347,,climate change,0.9203855991363525,neutral,0.5406368374824524
2016/06/28_09:35,Congratulations to D.C. and thanks to Mayor Bowser and the D.C. Council for fighting to #RaiseTheWage.https://twitter.com/MayorBowser/status/747570324598824960 …,565,2153,"['D.C.' 'GPE'],['Bowser' 'PERSON'],['the D.C. Council' 'ORG'],['#RaiseTheWage.https://twitter.com/MayorBowser/status/747570324598824960'
 'WORK_OF_ART']",politics,0.5480492115020752,positive,0.8707669973373413
2016/06/28_08:35,She outworked her rivals ... and became a role model to millions of Americans—including our two daughters.  on Pat Summitt,3090,9991,"['Americans' 'NORP'],['Pat Summitt' 'PERSON']",family,0.5436617732048035,positive,0.5993718504905701
2016/06/26_16:25,We must keep working toward an America free from discrimination against LGBT individuals. #LoveIsLovepic.twitter.com/YxdiL21fIl,2342,7631,['America' 'GPE'],USA,0.6876583099365234,positive,0.5461156964302063
2016/06/26_15:13,President Obama designates the first national monument honoring the LGBT rights movement. http://ofa.bo/hAS6  #LoveIsLove,1145,3869,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.4803600013256073,positive,0.6473883986473083
2016/06/26_07:00,Stand in solidarity with LGBT Americans—add your name. http://ofa.bo/ycK  #LoveIsLove,601,2355,['Americans' 'NORP'],USA,0.6392582654953003,neutral,0.5243433713912964
2016/06/25_14:20,We've made enormous progress toward full equality for LGBT Americans. Let's keep it going. #LoveIsLovepic.twitter.com/x4mTOKQSiP,5299,16705,['Americans' 'NORP'],USA,0.600196123123169,positive,0.9169768691062927
2016/06/24_16:15,Take a look: @VP Biden discusses what 4-4 decisions—like yesterday's on immigration—mean for our country.https://amp.twimg.com/v/2fa50a48-ce91-4811-8f56-5dd3b78bc8a1 …,1322,3193,['Biden' 'PERSON'],politics,0.5970268249511719,neutral,0.8189153075218201
2016/06/24_14:12,From gun violence prevention to LGBT rights this grassroots movement is fighting for progress. Show your support:http://ofa.bo/iAKz ,770,2855,,USA,0.4443729817867279,positive,0.7191474437713623
2016/06/24_12:57,Stonewall will be our first national monument to tell the story of the struggle for LGBT rights. http://ofa.bo/uaC ,1319,3630,['Stonewall' 'FAC'],USA,0.6107003092765808,neutral,0.7140263319015503
2016/06/24_08:33,Because Senate leaders refuse to do their jobs the Supreme Court cannot properly do its job. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/DvqUdLN2pA,6462,13404,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['the Supreme Court' 'ORG']",business,0.4695656895637512,negative,0.7662574648857117
2016/06/23_14:02,Congress: Listen to the millions of voices demanding a vote on efforts to reduce gun violence. #DisarmHatepic.twitter.com/X2uYxbJSs0,4788,13750,['Congress' 'ORG'],politics,0.5068286061286926,neutral,0.5281911492347717
2016/06/23_08:53,LIVE: President Obama is speaking about today's Supreme Court immigration ruling. http://ofa.bo/gAK1  #ImmigrationAction,453,1447,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",USA,0.41137591004371643,neutral,0.8471988439559937
2016/06/22_18:30,We need more than moments of silence. We need action. And that's what's going on in the House now: http://ofa.bo/yc8  #NoBillNoBreak,6546,17167,['House' 'ORG'],business,0.47349613904953003,neutral,0.6863791346549988
2016/06/22_08:16,If you're one of the millions of Americans who believes Judge Garland should get a fair hearing add your voice: http://ofa.bo/xa6,1232,3553,"['Americans' 'NORP'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",USA,0.5871855020523071,neutral,0.7558732032775879
2016/06/21_15:02,Judge Merrick Garland just received the American Bar Association's highest rating:http://ofa.bo/c64P,1215,3713,"['Merrick Garland' 'PERSON'],[""the American Bar Association's"" 'ORG']",USA,0.5499582290649414,positive,0.6292591094970703
2016/06/21_13:52,Say you support decisive action to tackle climate change. http://ofa.bo/vb1  #ActOnClimate,477,1685,,climate change,0.8458625078201294,neutral,0.6775467991828918
2016/06/20_09:09,Take a look at President Obama's interview with @NatGeo on national parks climate change and more.http://ofa.bo/vam ,724,2593,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@NatGeo' 'ORG']",climate change,0.7166347503662109,neutral,0.7997884750366211
2016/06/19_10:59,To me fatherhood means being there. http://ofa.bo/e63s,1916,6539,,family,0.5911238789558411,neutral,0.6254276037216187
2016/06/19_09:49,Happy Father's Day to all the dads out there.pic.twitter.com/okqSRnQk6n,11325,43474,,family,0.8737127184867859,positive,0.9793685674667358
2016/06/18_16:28,In the weekly address the President talks about setting examples for children in light of tragedies like Orlando.http://ofa.bo/fAJO ,783,3074,,USA,0.4131702184677124,neutral,0.6796704530715942
2016/06/18_08:31,President Obama has taken unprecedented steps to protect our land and water for future generations.pic.twitter.com/D5PNr4itC5,5016,20529,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.4553072452545166,positive,0.7354574799537659
2016/06/13_09:52,#OrlandoUnitedpic.twitter.com/ixCxMZzGH2,7511,16708,,USA,0.5141213536262512,neutral,0.8977025151252747
2016/06/10_13:56,Minds open. Hearts change. America shifts.  #Pride2016http://www.snappytv.com/tc/2118901,17732,33944,['America' 'GPE'],USA,0.828315258026123,positive,0.5654914975166321
2016/06/10_12:53,Today #LoveIsLove in all 50 states. But millions of Americans are still fighting to end discrimination—join them: http://ofa.bo/uZC,5559,11663,['Americans' 'NORP'],USA,0.735690176486969,positive,0.5013185739517212
2016/06/09_17:43,Watch President Obama Slow Jam the News on @FallonTonight at 11:35 p.m. ET. #POTUSonFallonpic.twitter.com/RuwpGwbTSA,1602,7940,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@FallonTonight' 'WORK_OF_ART']",politics,0.5907308459281921,neutral,0.8104435801506042
2016/06/07_14:57,Senate leaders' refusal to give Judge Garland a fair hearing is pure politics. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/8rzLIBigzM,3826,10553,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.9835830330848694,negative,0.5921810269355774
2016/06/07_11:33,"Senate leaders' politicization of the Supreme Court is ""unconscionable."" http://ofa.bo/xYB  #DoYourJob",670,2090,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['the Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.9385064244270325,negative,0.650553286075592
2016/06/07_09:58,Love looks good on you. Wear it with pride: http://ofa.bo/fAHy  #LoveIsLovepic.twitter.com/g5WjqYQvHq,583,2340,,USA,0.4619236886501312,positive,0.9601283669471741
2016/06/06_10:00,Former Energy Secretary @GovRichardson: Why the #TPP will make a difference in fighting climate change.http://ofa.bo/d62l,399,1769,"['Energy' 'ORG'],['@GovRichardson' 'PERSON'],['TPP' 'LAW']",climate change,0.8735557198524475,neutral,0.7280482649803162
2016/06/03_13:45,The Supreme Court shouldn't be part of partisan political games. Add your name if you agree: http://ofa.bo/jAE0,775,2458,['The Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.7145559787750244,neutral,0.49215102195739746
2016/06/02_11:08,Join the thousands of people calling on Congress to do something about gun violence—add your name: http://ofa.bo/yYs  #WearOrange,1513,3794,['Congress' 'ORG'],politics,0.5696200132369995,neutral,0.6816943287849426
2016/06/02_09:53,Gun violence takes far too many lives in America. Congress needs to act. #WearOrangepic.twitter.com/TYqb1fklcu,3313,8053,"['America' 'GPE'],['Congress' 'ORG']",USA,0.8046832084655762,negative,0.7650502324104309
2016/06/01_16:47,LAST CHANCE: Keep calm and enter before the midnight deadline. http://ofa.bo/a65f pic.twitter.com/RJxiN938k8,377,1380,,business,0.511384904384613,neutral,0.8039454221725464
2016/06/01_15:04,Speak out against gun violence— #WearOrange tomorrow. https://amp.twimg.com/v/43b27caf-3516-43d6-9a0e-93c956048e13 …,3346,4878,,USA,0.4660164415836334,neutral,0.6528052687644958
2016/06/01_12:31,LIVE: President Obama is speaking in Elkhart Indiana highlighting America's economic progress. http://ofa.bo/iAGR ,381,1177,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['Elkhart' 'GPE'],['Indiana' 'GPE'],['America' 'GPE']",USA,0.8760725855827332,neutral,0.7102704048156738
2016/06/01_08:19,You don't want to miss out on this opportunity—enter now before tonight's deadline. http://ofa.bo/d61P pic.twitter.com/VpuEcqR86Z,584,2495,,business,0.4081863760948181,positive,0.5407958626747131
2016/05/31_13:12,The Supreme Court shouldn't be part of partisan political games. Add your name if you agree: http://ofa.bo/iAFx ,694,2007,['The Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.6963897943496704,neutral,0.4800911247730255
2016/05/31_08:21,Share a laugh with President Obama—enter now for your chance. http://ofa.bo/gAF8 pic.twitter.com/JkBo1fVrJ0,458,1613,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.4432431161403656,neutral,0.5062386989593506
2016/05/27_14:26,A new survey shows that the overwhelming majority of #Obamacare customers are satisfied with their plans: http://ofa.bo/gAF2,906,2962,['#Obamacare' 'LAW'],health,0.6629946827888489,positive,0.8299048542976379
2016/05/25_12:14,Senate leaders need to stop obstructing our Supreme Court—add your name if you agree: http://ofa.bo/gAEO  #DoYourJob,551,1635,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.4741903841495514,neutral,0.5496715307235718
2016/05/24_14:47,If you think Senate leaders should do their jobs and fill the #SCOTUS vacancy add your name now: http://ofa.bo/gADc ,607,2024,['Senate' 'ORG'],politics,0.6140924096107483,neutral,0.6883206963539124
2016/05/24_11:29,People want Senate to act on Supreme Court vacancy. See what editorial boards are saying: http://ofa.bo/fADi  #DoYourJob,481,1552,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.5100420117378235,neutral,0.769008457660675
2016/05/24_10:08,Ever wished you could meet President Obama? Here's your chance. http://ofa.bo/jAA4 pic.twitter.com/AeFMTtBdf9,665,2912,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.4514336585998535,neutral,0.6169640421867371
2016/05/24_08:58,Judge Garland has one of the most impressive resumes of any Supreme Court nominee in recent history.https://amp.twimg.com/v/1ef21d28-e40a-4a92-b998-64b42041bfd7 …,1820,5317,"['Garland' 'PERSON'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",USA,0.4212842583656311,positive,0.9096196293830872
2016/05/23_10:17,Editorial boards to senators: #DoYourJob and fill the Supreme Court vacancy. http://ofa.bo/fACu ,521,1677,['Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.47188812494277954,neutral,0.7404101490974426
2016/05/20_13:51,Check out editorials from across the country calling on senators to fill the Supreme Court vacancy: http://ofa.bo/e5wp  #DoYourJob,716,2184,['Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.6826327443122864,neutral,0.8195066452026367
2016/05/20_08:46,Despite Judge Garland's qualifications some Senate leaders still refuse to give him a hearing—speak out: http://ofa.bo/c5x9,597,1705,"['Garland' 'PERSON'],['Senate' 'ORG']",politics,0.5888949632644653,negative,0.6470099091529846
2016/05/19_09:02,Stand up for middle-class workers—add your name to support the Obama administration's new #overtime rule: http://ofa.bo/fABk ,441,1667,,politics,0.6342218518257141,neutral,0.6374942660331726
2016/05/18_15:03,Marriage equality? Affordable health care? Or economic progress? Tell him in person: http://ofa.bo/fABW pic.twitter.com/F83AdfUC8H,516,2517,,health,0.6101253032684326,neutral,0.7643992900848389
2016/05/18_11:53,LIVE: @VP Biden is speaking about the economy at @jenisicecreams headquarters in Ohio. http://ofa.bo/iAC0,231,948,"['@VP Biden' 'PERSON'],['@jenisicecreams' 'ORG'],['Ohio' 'GPE']",business,0.39306640625,neutral,0.8213649988174438
2016/05/18_08:35,LIVE: Senate Judiciary Democrats are holding a forum on Judge Merrick Garland.http://ofa.bo/yUa ,439,1599,"['Senate Judiciary' 'ORG'],['Democrats' 'NORP'],['Merrick Garland.http://ofa.bo/yUa' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5551085472106934,neutral,0.8692955374717712
2016/05/17_14:58,Here's your chance: Tell President Obama what you're most thankful for—in person. http://ofa.bo/yUS pic.twitter.com/lxFIDqbclW,660,3235,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.907498300075531,positive,0.6069281697273254
2016/05/17_10:15,Senate leaders are continuing to obstruct a fair hearing for Judge Garland—help put the pressure on: http://ofa.bo/b60r  #DoYourJob,511,1559,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5918740630149841,negative,0.728424608707428
2016/05/17_08:11,It's time for Senate leaders to put politics aside and fill the Supreme Court vacancy. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/UAhLXYqgTN,2768,8773,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.5881781578063965,neutral,0.7217811942100525
2016/05/16_14:48,April was the seventh consecutive month of record-high temperatures. We need to #ActOnClimate.http://ofa.bo/c5vH,1949,3618,,climate change,0.9194885492324829,neutral,0.529740035533905
2016/05/16_13:53,Think Senate leaders should do their jobs and give Judge Garland a fair hearing? Add your name: http://ofa.bo/c5vF  #DoYourJob,478,1613,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.48386284708976746,neutral,0.7438402771949768
2016/05/16_11:58,LIVE: President Obama is speaking with @BuzzFeed about his #SCOTUS nominee Judge Merrick Garland.http://ofa.bo/c5vE,349,1368,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['@BuzzFeed' 'ORG'],['SCOTUS' 'ORG'],['Merrick Garland.http://ofa.bo/c5vE' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5653591752052307,neutral,0.8861334323883057
2016/05/16_09:06,We need to lead this fight. #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/ArdxyYdCiN,637,2096,,climate change,0.8927897810935974,neutral,0.6690204739570618
2016/05/13_14:01,Show your support for continued efforts to tackle climate change: http://ofa.bo/b60k  #ActOnClimate,430,1455,,climate change,0.8997988700866699,positive,0.7132178544998169
2016/05/13_11:33,Senate leaders should listen to the American people. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/vArMxcZh5W,2265,5836,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['American' 'NORP']",USA,0.469723105430603,neutral,0.6611090898513794
2016/05/13_08:31,Find out what Judge Merrick Garland's former clerks have to say about his record as a public servant: http://ofa.bo/c5v4,555,2218,['Merrick Garland' 'PERSON'],USA,0.4173636734485626,neutral,0.825935959815979
2016/05/12_12:16,Add your name if you support big steps forward in the fight to tackle climate change: http://ofa.bo/z0TF  #ActOnClimate,445,1473,,climate change,0.8596344590187073,positive,0.6017608046531677
2016/05/11_09:17,Here's where editorial boards across the country stand when it comes to the #SCOTUS vacancy: http://ofa.bo/z0T2  #DoYourJob,469,1718,,politics,0.5258901715278625,neutral,0.8371952772140503
2016/05/10_13:59,Senate leaders: #DoYourJob and give Judge Garland the fair hearing he deserves.pic.twitter.com/sg3Zx4vzIM,1693,5814,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",business,0.43971818685531616,neutral,0.7634896636009216
2016/05/10_11:55,Join the hundreds of thousands of people calling on Senate leaders to give Judge Garland a fair hearing: http://ofa.bo/gA8l,594,1836,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Garland' 'PERSON']",politics,0.5014469623565674,neutral,0.791591227054596
2016/05/10_09:16,Judge Garland has impeccable credentials—he deserves a fair hearing from the Senate. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/vqtTB1J4hL,3107,8721,"['Garland' 'PERSON'],['Senate' 'ORG']",business,0.4730428159236908,positive,0.7413472533226013
2016/05/09_10:24,Partisan obstructionism shouldn't hold back our Supreme Court. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/Q7rRKyWlZc,1244,4151,['Supreme Court' 'ORG'],politics,0.6051681637763977,negative,0.48168185353279114
2016/05/08_10:26,This Mother’s Day say thank you. Say 'I love you.' http://ofa.bo/uRT ,1761,6564,,family,0.8496931195259094,positive,0.9278536438941956
2016/05/06_14:05,Add your name if you think Senate leaders need to stop obstructing our Supreme Court: http://ofa.bo/d5vs  #DoYourJob,794,2778,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.48251450061798096,neutral,0.5355876088142395
2016/05/06_09:45,74 consecutive months—more than six years—of private-sector job growth. Let's keep up the progress.pic.twitter.com/igXXN83jCy,2754,8357,,business,0.7022678256034851,positive,0.8427845239639282
2016/05/06_09:16,LIVE: President Obama is speaking about the economy and new steps to strengthen financial transparency. http://ofa.bo/d5vq,368,1324,['Obama' 'PERSON'],finance,0.4970329999923706,neutral,0.6377168893814087
2016/05/06_06:39,The economy added 160000 jobs in April—a record-breaking 74 months of private-sector job growth.,1570,4952,,business,0.42656394839286804,positive,0.868720531463623
2016/05/04_15:12,President Obama: When American workers and businesses compete on a level playing field no one can beat us.http://ofa.bo/uRJ ,859,2959,"['Obama' 'PERSON'],['American' 'NORP']",USA,0.4582269787788391,neutral,0.614881157875061
2016/05/04_11:00,Retweet if you agree. #DoYourJobpic.twitter.com/WjTM07LRL4,4415,5868,,business,0.49104043841362,neutral,0.7173764109611511
2016/05/03_13:33,LIVE: President Obama honors the 2016 National Teacher of the Year. http://ofa.bo/uRI,396,1381,['Obama' 'PERSON'],USA,0.5039483904838562,positive,0.6730470657348633
2016/05/03_10:44,Good climate change policy and good economic policy can go hand in hand. #ActOnClimatepic.twitter.com/MEDMB870SP,2142,6951,,climate change,0.9395982027053833,positive,0.5915045142173767
2016/05/03_09:40,American workers deserve a trade agreement that works for them. Check out President Obama's op-ed on #TPP:http://ofa.bo/jA5s,682,2698,"['American' 'NORP'],['Obama' 'PERSON'],['TPP' 'EVENT']",USA,0.4710000157356262,neutral,0.5450345873832703
2016/05/03_07:00,The United States just hit one million solar installations—enough to power 5.5 million homes. #MillionSolarStrong,2158,6527,['The United States' 'GPE'],USA,0.8885131478309631,positive,0.6698297262191772
2016/05/02_13:08,Building a clean energy economy is a great way to #ActOnClimate for people across the country.pic.twitter.com/xfdVKh3Zhy,1323,4882,,climate change,0.8067206740379333,positive,0.9400067329406738
2016/05/02_08:59,It's unacceptable for obstructionists in the Senate to play political games with the Supreme Court. Say you agree: http://ofa.bo/d5vM,875,2440,"['Senate' 'ORG'],['the Supreme Court' 'ORG']",politics,0.8806605339050293,negative,0.803450882434845
